find
探す
Ask
聞く
I would like to welcome everyone to participate today
本日は皆様のご参加をお待ちしております
we tonight
私たちは今夜
Speech at the Knowledge Feast of the Institute of Public Studies
公共学研究所の知識の饗宴でのスピーチ
Everyone has seen the title of our speech today
今日のスピーチのタイトルは誰もが見たでしょう
First of all, I would like to introduce our speaker today
まず初めに、今日のスピーカーを紹介したいと思います
The protagonist is our Dr. Xu Wenlian
主人公は徐文蓮博士です。
The current Institute of Information Science
現在の情報科学研究所
Special researcher and director
特品研究員兼所長
Director Xu was in 1973
徐監督は1973年
Graduated from National Taiwan University Department of Mathematics
国立台湾大学数学科卒業
in 1979
1979年に
Cornell University
コーネル大学
He is a Ph.D. in Operational Studies
彼は運用研究の博士号を取得しています。
Because it is Operation Research
オペレーションリサーチだから
in 1980
1980年
Taught at Northwestern University
ノースウェスタン大学で教鞭をとる
Got a permanent offer
永久オファーを獲得しました
but probably feel
でもおそらく感じる
Should be returning home to serve
家に帰って奉仕するべきだ
So in 1989 when
それで1989年に
back to
戻る
Academia Sinica Information Service
中央研究院情報サービス
Now the director of the Information Office
現在は情報局の局長
When Professor Xu was at Northwestern University in his early days
徐教授が初期のノースウェスタン大学にいた頃
His research focuses on
彼の研究は次のことに焦点を当てています
The Theory of Mindful Algorithm
マインドフルアルゴリズムの理論
His two papers on planar perfect graphs
平面完全グラフに関する彼の 2 つの論文
is a classic in this field
この分野では古典的です
He is also working in computational biology
彼は計算生物学の研究にも取り組んでいます
In the analysis and alignment of DNA sequences
DNA配列の解析と比較において
Many error-dissolving algorithms have been designed
多くのエラー解決アルゴリズムが設計されています
According to the series of proteins
プロテインのシリーズに合わせて
Prediction of function and structure
機能と構造の予測
Analysis of Hezhipuyi Therapeutic Medicine
和子溥治療医学の分析
after he returns home
彼が家に帰った後
Continuing research on these theoretical aspects
これらの理論的側面についての継続的な研究
Then also take the experience of these algorithms
次に、これらのアルゴリズムの経験も取り入れてください
Applied in Chinese natural language research
中国語の自然言語研究に応用
and system development
そしてシステム開発
Then developed the intelligent
その後、インテリジェントな
Make sound input method
做音輸入法
So in 1993 published the state-run input method
そこで 1993 年に国営入力方式を発表しました。
Won the first Top Ten Outstanding Chinese Information Products Award
第 1 回中国情報製品トップ 10 優秀賞を受賞
Then published the natural input method in 1995
その後、1995 年にナチュラルインプットメソッドを発表しました。
These experiences of subsequent artificial intelligence research
その後の人工知能研究の経験
Also applied to the Internet for Chinese question answering system
インターネットの中国語質問応答システムにも応用
So with robotics research
ロボット研究に関しても同様です
So we might hear something about that today
だから今日それについて何か聞くかもしれない
These studies have implications for building large-scale language application systems in industry
これらの研究は、産業における大規模な言語アプリケーション システムの構築に影響を及ぼします。
For example, online customer service
たとえば、オンラインカスタマーサービス
Sentiment analysis of Q&A opinions within the enterprise
社内のQ&A意見のセンチメント分析
Or product recommendations, etc. are very suitable
または製品の推奨事項などが非常に適しています
Professor Xu's outstanding research
徐教授の優れた研究
He has received three National Science Council Distinguished Awards
彼は全米学術会議特別賞を3回受賞している
Then won the first Li Guoding Chuanshi Award
その後、第一回李国定伝士賞を受賞
There is also the American IEEE
アメリカのIEEEもあります
is a meeting of an association
協会の会合です
There are many awards from the Pan Wenyuan Research Association for the Central Plains Award
潘文源研究協会からは中原賞を多数受賞
2012 Information Medal of Honor from the Information Society of the Republic of China
2012 年中華民国情報学会より情報名誉勲章を受賞
So in addition to his cognition in the Central Plains Academy
したがって、セントラルプレーンズアカデミーでの彼の認識に加えて、
Also served as the chairman of the Republic of China Society for Artificial Intelligence
中華民国人工知能学会会長も務めた
and the chairman of the Institute of Computational Linguistics, etc.
計算言語学研究所理事長など
Say a lot about service experience
サービス体験について多くのことを語る
Has a track record of award-winning research
受賞歴のある研究実績あり
So our Knowledge Award Academy hopes to say
したがって、私たちのKnowledge Award Academyはこう言いたいのです。
Introduce to everyone the comparatively contacted research in the Central Plains Institute
セントラルプレーンズ研究所の比較的連絡の多い研究を皆さんに紹介します
Then I hope to be able to say in a more common language
そうすればもっと共通言語で言えるようになりたいです
Introduce to the public what we are doing with this research
この研究で私たちが行っていることを一般に紹介します
So today we see that the topic of this speech is about
さて、今日のこのスピーチのテーマは、
The field of artificial intelligence is probably
人工知能の分野はおそらく
A field that was only founded 60 years ago
わずか60年前に設立されたばかりの分野
You can see that it has largely fallen in the past 60 years
過去60年間で大幅に減少していることがわかります
just nerves are very hot
ただ神経がとても熱いです
Then there was a period of time when the development was slower
その後、開発が遅れた時期もありました
But recently because of deep learning
でも最近はディープラーニングのせいで
So in this area it's re-emphasizing
したがって、この分野では、それが再度強調されています
So we are talking about Artificial Intelligence in this
したがって、この記事では人工知能について話しています。
artificial intelligence
人工知能
There have been many other recent developments related to
関連する最近の出来事は他にもたくさんあります
It makes everyone in the academic world have some new perceptions of this field
学術界の誰もがこの分野について新たな認識を持つようになります
We also saw in the newspaper recently that there is Google's Appagope
Google の Appagope があることも最近新聞で知りました。
We put Weiqi some national players
ウェイチーに代表選手を何人か入れました
The world's masters are all defeated
世界のマスターは全員敗北しました
So it is to use a concept of deep learning
つまり、ディープラーニングの概念を使用することになります
Only then did such great results be achieved
そうして初めてこのような素晴らしい結果が得られたのです
So let's start now by saying we want to be able to
それでは、できるようになりたいと言うことから始めましょう
To predict when we can use these
これらをいつ使用できるかを予測するには
APAGO's Language Prediction System
APAGOの言語予測システム
understand the system
システムを理解する
So in this speech
そこでこのスピーチでは
we'll see some introduction to this
これについては少し紹介します
So natural language understanding
つまり自然言語理解
Is the last level of artificial intelligence
人工知能の最後のレベルです
So I think Xu Shuochang is right about this topic
したがって、この件については Xu Shuochang の意見が正しいと思います。
I won't say more
これ以上は言いません
We will listen to Xu Shuochang's speech
徐碩昌氏のスピーチを聞きます
see what is called
いわゆるものを見てください
The final hurdle of artificial intelligence
人工知能の最後のハードル
so we now
だから私たちは今
I hope everyone with the warmest applause
皆様に温かい拍手をお願いします
Come and welcome our host today
今日は私たちのホストを歓迎しに来てください
Introduction by Vice President Zhou
周副社長による紹介
Thank you all for coming
お越しいただきありがとうございました
I have this opportunity to share with you
この機会を皆さんと共有したいと思います
So many years of research
長年にわたる研究
i remember ten years ago
10年前のことを覚えています
I also talked about the feast of knowledge here, and I also talked about artificial intelligence
ここでは知識の饗宴についても話しましたし、人工知能についても話しました
But the progress of the past ten years is actually very dramatic
しかし、過去 10 年間の進歩は実際には非常に劇的です
So I would like to share my personal research experience on language
そこで、言語に関する私の個人的な研究経験を共有したいと思います。
This research will actually have a great impact on everyone, especially young people
この研究は実際、すべての人、特に若者に大きな影響を与えるでしょう
Because in the future, if the ability of computers to understand natural language increases, many jobs will disappear
なぜなら、将来、コンピュータの自然言語理解能力が向上すれば、多くの仕事がなくなるからです。
We can now see that Hon Hai claims to have an army of 40 million in the mainland, and tens of thousands of them are robots
ホンハイが本土に4,000万人の軍隊を持っていると主張しており、そのうちの数万人がロボットであることがわかります。
His entire factory is now called a factory without lights, and there is no need to turn on the lights at all.
現在、彼の工場全体は無照明工場と呼ばれており、照明を付ける必要がまったくありません。
can get things done from start to finish
最初から最後まで物事を成し遂げることができる
So in the future when the white-collar class handles paperwork in the office, the computer can help you write and read letters
つまり、将来、ホワイトカラー層がオフィスで事務処理を行うとき、コンピュータは手紙を書いたり読んだりするのに役立つようになるでしょう。
Of course, that level is relatively shallow, but he can do a lot of secretarial things
もちろん、そのレベルは少し浅いですが、秘書的なことはたくさんできます
This is a future one, it will happen within five years
これは未来の話で、5年以内に起こるでしょう
So I now name this as the final level of artificial intelligence
そこで私はこれを人工知能の最終レベルと名付けます
Because everyone knows that computers have also made rapid progress in vision recently.
というのも、最近コンピュータの視覚も急速に進歩していることは誰もが知っているからです。
Can tell cats and dogs apart which means it doesn't need much of these people's intervention
犬と猫を区別できるため、人の介入がほとんど必要ありません
it can be done
それはできる
But it's far from there
でもそこからは遠い
Speech is progressing rapidly
スピーチは急速に進歩しています
Now everyone has used Google's audiobook
今では誰もが Google のオーディオブックを使用しています
or Siri's voicebook is known to be very accurate
または Siri のボイスブックは非常に正確であることが知られています
It's just that it doesn't understand
それが理解できないだけです
In most cases it just uses other technologies to correct the speech
ほとんどの場合、音声を修正するために他のテクノロジーを使用するだけです
but it doesn't understand what you're talking about
しかしそれはあなたが何を言っているのか理解できません
So let's take a look today
それでは今日も見てみましょう
This is to understand what you are talking about
これはあなたが話していることを理解するためのものです
how difficult is this
これはどれくらい難しいですか
So my Daeko is like this today
というわけで今日の大子はこんな感じです
I'll start with a simple personal brevity
まずは個人的な簡単な説明から始めます
then artificial intelligence
それから人工知能
natural language understanding
自然言語理解
The last thing is to say which jobs will be replaced by computers
最後に、どの仕事がコンピュータに取って代わられるかということだ。
personally
個人的に
Since I was a child, I prefer to use my brain rather than my hands.
子供の頃から手を使うよりも頭を使うほうが好きでした。
i often think
私はよく思います
At that time, of course
その時はもちろん
All of our environments are very
私たちの環境はすべて非常に優れています
Very difficult to do a lot of automated things
多くのことを自動化するのは非常に困難
I'm studying mathematics in college and it's a good training
私は大学で数学を勉強しています、それは良い訓練です
Because I find the theories that are the most difficult to say
なぜなら私は理論を言うのが最も難しいと思うからです
Probably we've all been through it and don't necessarily say it's a good read
おそらく誰もが経験したことがあると思いますが、必ずしも良い読書だとは言えません
But we at least after
しかし、少なくともその後は
go to other fields
他の分野に行く
No threshold does not mean easy
閾値がないからといって簡単というわけではない
It means that your mathematics is basically fearless
それはあなたの数学が基本的に恐れ知らずであることを意味します
Well, it's actually not easy for many people.
まあ、実際には多くの人にとってそれは簡単ではありません。
So early artificial intelligence
とても初期の人工知能
is proved by logic and theorem
論理と定理で証明される
The earliest artificial intelligence actually has very few systems
初期の人工知能には実際にはほとんどシステムがありませんでした
because then you know
なぜなら、それならわかるから
Computers are really underpowered
コンピュータは本当に能力が低い
When I was studying at National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学に留学していた頃
whole school
学校全体
What is the memory of the computer in National Taiwan University?
国立台湾大学のコンピュータにはどれくらいのメモリが搭載されていますか?
Can you guess it?
推測できますか？
Now we may be 16GB
今は16GBになるかもしれない
that is 16K
それは16Kです
Not 16K sorry
16Kじゃなくてごめんなさい
16GB
16ギガバイト
Just 16GB can't do anything at all
16GBじゃ何もできない
So I used to do theory
それで私は理論をやっていました
Do theory
理論を実行する
Syneron Puffing is the automatic proof of theorem
Syneron パフィングは定理の自動的な証明です
This was very popular before
これ、前にすごく流行ってたんですよ
There is a famous professor in our country
私たちの国に有名な教授がいます
in doing this
これを行う中で
very old professor
とても年配の教授
Do you know who it is?
誰だか知っていますか？
very famous
非常に有名
Professor Li Jiatong
李家彤教授
he doesn't mention it now
彼は今はそのことについては言及していません
Because he did it then and later he
彼はその時もやったし、その後もそうしたから
I think he kind of hates the field
彼はその分野が嫌いだと思う
He thinks that automatic proof is too difficult
彼は自動証明は難しすぎると考えている
So in the future, he will treat people who do AI
だから将来的にはAIをやる人々を治療するだろう
a little disgusted
少しうんざりした
Thanks
ありがとう
At that time, AI academics talked more and did less
当時、AI 学者はより多くのことを語り、より少ないことを行っていました
this is impossible
不可能だよ
Because the computer age was very slow at that time
当時はコンピューターの時代が非常に遅かったので、
We should have written this 30 years ago
これを30年前に書くべきだった
I made a mistake in the constant number 30 years ago
30年前に定数を間違えた
I went there in 1980 when I was teaching at Northwestern University
私は 1980 年にノースウェスタン大学で教えていたときにそこに行きました
In 1982, I saw the first Datong green screen
1982年、私は最初の大同グリーンスクリーンを見ました
If you're old enough to know
わかるくらいの年齢なら
The first generation of IPM computers
第一世代の IPM コンピュータ
The hardware is almost all made by Datong
ハードウェアはほぼすべて大同製です
So its little screen is a green
つまり、その小さな画面は緑色です
Appeared in 1982
1982年に登場
This caused a great shock in Western countries
これは西側諸国に大きな衝撃を与えた
Almost all typewriters disappeared within half a year
半年以内にほぼすべてのタイプライターが姿を消した
I used to use electric typewriters
以前は電動タイプライターを使っていました
Later, it was all replaced by computer screens.
その後、すべてがコンピューターの画面に置き換えられました。
Even kindergarten kids can play by themselves
幼稚園児でも一人で遊べる
So this is a very natural thing in pinyin countries
つまり、ピンインの国ではこれはごく自然なことなのです
Because it only has 26 keys and 26 subtitles, it can type out all languages
26 個のキーと 26 個の字幕しかないため、すべての言語を入力できます
But Chinese is extremely difficult
でも中国語ってすごく難しいんです
At that time, professional typing companies were using the Changjie input method.
当時、プロのタイピング会社は Changjie 入力方法を使用していました。
Now you may rarely hear that you have to recite those Changjie horses.
今では、長傑馬を暗唱しなければならないという話を聞くことはほとんどないかもしれません。
Changjie input method
昌傑輸入法
The Zhuyin input method was immature at that time
当時の注音入力方法は未熟でした
is very high error rate
エラー率が非常に高い
Therefore, we hope to develop automatic phonetic selection input in foreign countries.
したがって、私たちは海外でも読み自動選択入力を開発したいと考えています。
We often compare a person who can't type Chinese
私たちはよく中国語の入力ができない人と比較します。
It's a foreigner on a computer
パソコンの中の外国人です
That is, he still needs translation when facing the computer
つまり、コンピュータに向かうときも翻訳が必要です
At that time, we had many teachers who received
当時、受けた先生もたくさんいました。
Both English and English can be typed
英語も英語も入力可能
This wasn’t in 1982, probably when I returned to Taiwan in 1990
これは 1982 年ではなく、おそらく 1990 年に台湾に戻ったときのものでした。
He can type all English letters without any problem.
彼はすべての英語の文字を問題なく入力できます。
But as soon as he comes across Chinese, he prints it out
しかし、中国語を見つけるとすぐに印刷してしまいます。
and write his reply on it
そしてそこに彼の返事を書きます
Then ask the secretary to type the reply letter into Chinese and send it out
それから秘書に返事の手紙を中国語でタイプして送ってもらいます。
So earlier
だからもっと前に
Almost all secretaries will participate in the input method
ほぼすべての秘書が入力方式に参加します
that's why
それが理由です
I think communicating with the computer is a very important communication
パソコンとのコミュニケーションはとても大切なコミュニケーションだと思います
If a country is productive
国が生産的であれば
You can communicate with the computer only when you use English
英語を使用する場合のみコンピュータと通信できます
Chinese is not good at all
中文完全不行
this is a very poor one
これは非常に悪いものです
So we spent a lot of time doing Chinese
それで私たちは中国語に多くの時間を費やしました
But the first thing I did was because I needed to type Chinese
でも最初にやったのは、中国語を入力する必要があったからです
i saw that jubangful early
ジュバンフルを早く見ました
How does he do that reference input method
彼はその参照入力方法をどのように行うのでしょうか
But I don't want to recite that section
でもその部分は暗唱したくない
I have another problem when I fight Zhu Ying
Zhu Yingと戦うときに別の問題が発生します
It's the current standard keyboard
現在の標準キーボードです
is four rows
4行です
English English playing is three rows
英語 英語遊びは3列です
all in the middle
全部真ん中にある
and very
そして、非常に
It is very convenient
とても便利です
So I was
だから私はそうだった
At the beginning, I made this natural input method
最初にこの自然な入力メソッドを作成しました
One reason is because I don't like using the standard keyboard
理由の 1 つは、標準キーボードを使用するのが好きではないからです。
I must develop a keyboard of my own
独自のキーボードを開発する必要がある
So then there was a Xu-style keyboard
そこで登場したのが Xu スタイルのキーボードです
then me
それから私
I'll talk about it later, back to the Central Plains in 1989 with Mr. Chen Kejian
それについては後で話します。1989 年の中原で陳科堅氏と話した話に戻ります。
He is a very senior research scholar in our field
彼は私たちの分野では非常に上級の研究者です
In 1991, an initial heart system was probably established.
1991 年に、おそらく最初の心臓システムが確立されました。
Then when we made it in 1991
それから1991年にそれを作ったとき
Probably until the information month of 1992
おそらく1992年の情報月間まで
We didn't really launch a product until December
12月まで実際に製品を発売しませんでした
It was also written by an outside company for me.
これも外部の会社が私のために書いたものです。
Because we have no idea how to write such a commercial system
なぜなら、私たちはそのような商用システムの書き方がわからないからです。
The system used at that time may not have been heard by most of you
当時使用されていたシステムについては、ほとんどの人が聞いたことがないかもしれません。
called DOS
DOSと呼ばれる
The memory of the entire computer in the DOS system can only control 640K
DOS システムのコンピュータ全体のメモリは 640K しか制御できません
640K less than a Mega
メガより 640K 少ない
Now we have a Mega for every photo
これで、すべての写真に Mega が追加されました
Its entire computer is 640K
コンピューター全体は 640K
So you're going to make a sulva, squeeze it in this
それで、サルバを作るつもりです、これに押し込んでください
Then all the rules of all the warehouses must be entered.
次に、すべての倉庫のすべてのルールを入力する必要があります。
very difficult, so the theory I did
非常に難しいので、私がやった理論は
This algorithm helps a lot with this
このアルゴリズムはこれに非常に役立ちます
So we mourned the name in natural calligraphy in 1990
そこで私たちは1990年にその名前を自然な書道で追悼しました
By 1995, Microsoft hoped to be able to license our calligraphy
1995 年までに、マイクロソフトは私たちのカリグラフィーのライセンスを取得できるようにしたいと考えていました。
he speaks very well
彼はとても上手に話します
他說It's your honor to be used by
他說に利用していただけるのは光栄です
It is your honor to be placed in Microsoft, right?
Microsoft に入社できて光栄ですよね?
That means I don't really need to give you money.
つまり、本当にお金を渡す必要はないのです。
not that we want the money
お金が欲しいわけではありません
We think he probably wouldn't talk to the inventor like that in a foreign country
おそらく彼は外国では発明者にそのように話すことはないと思います
It's a very rude thing in my opinion.
私の意見では、それは非常に失礼なことです。
so we refuse
だから私たちは拒否します
Then we officially approved this funding in 1999 and downloaded it for free
その後、1999 年にこの資金提供を正式に承認し、無料でダウンロードしました
So it has been the champion of all downloaded software for seven consecutive weeks
つまり、7 週間連続ですべてのダウンロード ソフトウェアのチャンピオンとなっています。
Then my important calligraphy is to say
それでは、私の大切な書道はこう言います。
There is a Xu Zhijian card inside
中に徐志キーカードが入っています
All those who can type English but not Chinese when they come back from abroad
海外から帰ってきて、英語は打てるけど中国語は打てない人全員
It happens to be my training object
それはたまたま私のトレーニング対象です
So at that time, Chen Wenchun, the principal of Tsinghua University,
当時、清華大学校長の陳文春氏はこう言いました。
of course i want
もちろん欲しいです
Find someone older to teach
教えてくれる年上の人を探す
He really learned it in about ten minutes.
彼は本当に10分ほどでそれを学びました。
It's his correspondence with that Zhuyin
それはあのZhuyinとの文通だ
I remember it in ten minutes
10分もあれば覚えられる
There is also an alto director on the TV of the Ministry of Education
文科省のテレビにもアルトディレクターがいる
He said using the happy history is a growing professor
彼は、幸福な歴史を活用することが教授の成長であると述べた
He said I want to help you promote
彼はあなたのプロモーションを手伝いたいと言いました
I said you can't help me promote in academia
学術界での昇進には協力できないって言ったよ
that this is actually
これが実際にあるということ
transcribe
転写する
each of us
私たち一人ひとり
There are about five to fifteen homophones below Zhuyin
Zhuyin の下には約 5 ～ 15 個の同音異義語があります。
So you typed out ten words
それで、あなたは 10 個の単語を入力しました
That's a huge number of combinations
すごい組み合わせですね
if you don't understand
理解できない場合
this
これ
people who don't understand Chinese
中国語が分からない人
It's very difficult to spell it out
それを表現するのはとても難しいです
So now the audio book
さて、オーディオブックです
voice book words
ボイスブックの言葉
one tone below
一つ下の音
If you pronounce a sound, there may be
音を発音すると、
there are fifty to one hundred
50から100はあります
possible word
考えられる言葉
Because his confusion is high
彼の混乱は激しいので
So so many confusing words inside
中には紛らわしい単語がたくさんあります
To be able to turn him all right
彼をうまく変えることができるように
looks like
のように見える
mission impossible
ミッション・インポッシブル
Now you seem to Google me all at once
今あなたは私を一度にグーグル検索しているようです
In fact, there are many tricks in it
実はそこにはたくさんの裏技があるんです
So I talk about this current lack of understanding
そこで私はこの現在の理解の欠如について話します
It's just that I don't have a trick
ただ、コツがないんです
This system can be made quickly
このシステムはすぐに作れます
let me tell you now
今教えてください
You may understand right now
今なら分かるかも知れませんが
You put the information on this network
あなたはこのネットワークに情報を載せます
Every seven characters are memorized by a window
7文字ごとにウィンドウごとに記憶される
Then memorize the pinyin below it
次にその下のピンインを覚えてください
just like this
ちょうどこのような
After memorizing an article
記事を暗記した後
After memorizing about hundreds of thousands of articles
何十万もの記事を暗記した後
The combination of these words and pinyin you memorized
これらの単語と覚えたピンインの組み合わせ
take what anyone says
誰かの言うことを受け入れる
almost what he said
ほぼ彼の言ったことと同じ
There will be a part in the middle that is the same as this
真ん中にこれと同じ部分があります
right away
すぐに
So don't think Google is great
だからGoogleが素晴らしいとは思わないでください
It's actually quite a simple way
実はとても簡単な方法なんです
Then we are also working on the mobile version now
現在、モバイル版も開発中です
Both Chinese and English are preferred
中国語と英語の両方が望ましい
It is very convenient to type in English
英語を入力するのはとても便利です
You may not remember some English words firmly
いくつかの英単語をしっかりと覚えていない可能性があります
or it's too much trouble
あるいは面倒すぎる
like we have a biological DNA
私たちが生物学的な DNA を持っているのと同じように
The word DN is Doxyribonucle
DNという単語はドキシリボ核です
There are 13 letters
13文字あります
I don't want to go even if I beat you
倒しても行きたくない
One by one will make a mistake
一人ずつ間違いを犯すだろう
so our
だから私たちの
Because our system probably hits 3 or 4 keys
私たちのシステムはおそらく 3 つまたは 4 つのキーを押すためです
just type it out
それを入力するだけです
Let's start with the introduction of artificial intelligence
まずは人工知能の導入から始めましょう
In fact, in my previous profile, I have already put
実は、以前のプロフィールにすでに次のように書いています。
Some of my relationship with artificial intelligence
人工知能と私の関係の一部
have spoken out
声を上げた
Wait a minute we'll use the example
ちょっと待ってください、例を使用します
to explain more artificial intelligence
人工知能をさらに詳しく説明するには
How artificial intelligence first designed machines to
人工知能が最初に機械を設計した方法
simulated intelligence
模擬知能
This is actually very complicated
これは実際には非常に複雑です
How much do you want to simulate a human
どこまで人間を模倣したいのか
What we are talking about today is relatively simple
今日私たちが話していることは比較的単純です
It is to help human beings solve problems in life and work
それは人間の生活や仕事の問題を解決するのを助けることです
simple problem encountered
単純な問題が発生しました
I don't want to talk about that
それについては話したくない
Their Favorite Philosophers Talk About Conscious
彼らのお気に入りの哲学者が意識について語る
will he know he exists
彼は自分の存在を知っているだろうか
then will he have feelings
そうしたら彼は感情を持つだろうか
it's all very complicated
それはすべてとても複雑です
we are interested in saying
私たちは言うことに興味があります
Assistant-like functions can accept natural language instructions
アシスタントのような機能は自然言語の指示を受け入れることができます
able to do this
これができる
Many of our document processing is very simple
私たちの文書処理の多くは非常に簡単です
Like I often have problems when using PowerPoint
PowerPoint を使用するときによく問題が発生するように
i want this
これ欲しい
Like some screens are 19%
一部の画面は 19% のようです
169% is relatively wide
16%は比較的広い
Some screens are 40% to 30%
一部の画面は 40% ～ 30%
like this is 4 into 3
これは 4 に 3 です
Then I want to turn my slideshow into 16 to 9
次に、スライドショーを 16 対 9 にしたいと思います。
if he could understand
彼が理解できたら
I told him to turn the screen into 16 to 9
私は彼にこの画面を 16 対 9 にするように言いました
he will soon
彼はすぐにそうするだろう
If you read his manual
彼のマニュアルを読んでみると
Indicates how many keys to press
押すキーの数を示します
and that no one will know
そして誰も知らないだろう
So this is a very important
これは非常に重要なことです
So how to make software and home appliance manuals answer automatically
では、ソフトウェアや家電製品のマニュアルを自動的に回答させるにはどうすればよいでしょうか
The same goes for home appliances
家電製品も同様です
You buy a new cooler now
あなたは今新しいクーラーを購入します
right
右
Maybe that controller on the old chiller next to it
おそらくその隣の古い冷却装置のコントローラーでしょう
already familiar
すでにおなじみの
But new ones have to be learned again
しかし、新しいことはもう一度学ばなければなりません
then what we want is to say
それから私たちが言いたいのは
I told him it's too hot now
私は彼に今は暑すぎると言いました
It stops after two hours
2時間経つと止まる
How about turning it off an hour before I go to bed?
寝る1時間前に電源を切ってはどうでしょうか？
It doesn't matter what brand you are for this kind of thing
この種のことに関してはどのブランドかは関係ありません
I don't even need to read the manual if you can understand
理解できれば説明書を読む必要もありません
So the ideal in the future is to say that all these manuals disappear
ですので、将来的にはマニュアルが全部なくなるのが理想です。
completely unnecessary
全く不要な
The company's customer service staff don't need to answer questions.
同社のカスタマーサービススタッフは質問に答える必要はありません。
Then the Homepage made by each of us can conduct question and answer
そして、私たち一人ひとりが作ったホームページで質疑応答ができます
What does it mean
どういう意味ですか
Now the Homepage says when and where did you graduate from?
今、ホームページにはあなたがいつ、どこを卒業したのかが書かれています。
what are you doing?
あなたは何をしている？
Many people who are looking for a job hope that others can visit his webpage
仕事を探している多くの人は、他の人が彼のウェブページにアクセスできることを望んでいます。
This can be a passive one seeing
これは受動的な見方になる可能性があります
If you want to be proactive
積極的になりたいなら
People can ask questions on your website
人々はあなたのウェブサイト上で質問することができます
You don't even need to come to your website
ウェブサイトにアクセスする必要さえありません
just ask a question say
ただ質問して言ってください
Which school Xu Wennian graduated from, he can answer right away
徐文年がどこの学校を卒業したか、彼はすぐに答えることができます
So we're spending a lot of money now to make this page
このページを作るのに今多額のお金を費やしています
We're going to pay for this automated answer in the future
今後、この自動応答に対して料金を支払う予定です
but this automatic answer
しかし、この自動応答は
yes some packages
はい、いくつかのパッケージ
Just put your knowledge in it now
今すぐ知識を投入してください
it can answer
それは答えることができます
It's better that you don't need to spend any more money
これ以上お金をかけなくて良いのです
The following is the IoT
以下はIoTです
It is the devices of the Internet of Things
それはモノのインターネットのデバイスです
able to operate by itself
単独で動作できる
this is very important
これはとても重要です
So we talk about smart cities
そこでスマートシティについて話します
Smart families are talking about
賢い家族が話しているのは
A Natural Language Human-Machine Interface
自然言語によるヒューマン・マシン・インターフェース
All of these mechanized actions below
以下の機械化されたアクションはすべて
In fact, its difficulty is relatively low
実際、難易度は比較的低いです
The hardest thing is to understand what you want to do
一番難しいのは自分が何をしたいのかを理解することだ
So the field of artificial intelligence research
つまり、人工知能の研究分野は、
There are the following
以下のようなものがあります
Everyone is familiar with this
これは誰もがよく知っています
This is image processing
これは画像処理です
Then Graphics
次にグラフィックス
Next is the robot
次はロボットです
Then Speed ​​Recognition
次に高速認識
speech recognition natural language
音声認識自然言語
Then give up the whole language
それから言語全体を放棄する
search engine
検索エンジン
machine learning
機械学習
Data Mining
データマイニング
biological information
生体情報
These are all like AI
これらはすべてAIのようなものです
born of a child
子供から生まれた
at different times
さまざまな時に
but a few years ago
しかし数年前
5 years ago to ask people in these fields
5年前にこの分野の人たちに聞いてみた
He said I no longer do AI
彼は私はもうAIはやらないと言った
why do this
なぜこれをするのか
Can you figure it out?
分かりますか？
That is to say, AI used to have a very bad livelihood
つまり、AIは以前は非常に悪い生活を送っていたということです
Just because he gets too many research grants
研究助成金が多すぎるという理由だけで
Especially the funding of the U.S. military
特に米軍への資金提供
I don't know how much is invested in AI
AIにどれくらい投資されているか分からない
did not get any
何も得られなかった
very little benefit
メリットはほとんどない
So to be a scholar of AI
AIの学者になるには
There are many coming and going
行き来する人がたくさんいる
How many years has it been like this
こんなこと何年ぶりだろう
did not achieve his purpose
彼の目的は達成されなかった
like my wife used to talk about the stuff i made
妻が私が作ったものについて話していたように
He thinks this level is really not high enough
彼はこのレベルが実際には十分に高くないと考えている
I say it's already the best in the world
もう世界最高だと言うよ
that's useless
それは無駄です
It is true that the user does not know his technical details at all
ユーザーが自分の技術的な詳細をまったく知らないのは事実です
His pickiness is the truest
彼のこだわりは本物だ
Let's now look at the United States in this
ここで米国を見てみましょう
hollywood they do this
ハリウッド、彼らはこれをやる
Any new field his imagination is super shallow
新しい分野に対する彼の想像力は非常に浅い
So let's look at this
それではこれを見てみましょう
What the film industry expects from AI
映画業界が AI に期待するもの
2001 space exploration written, this was done in 1968, I don't know how many people read it
2001 年に書かれた宇宙探査、これは 1968 年に行われたものですが、何人が読んだかわかりません
At that time it was Stanley Kubrick, he wrote a supercomputer number HAL
当時それはスタンリー・キューブリックでした、彼はスーパーコンピューター番号HALを書きました
That is, the captain of the spaceship talks to the computer entirely by voice
つまり、宇宙船の船長はコンピュータと完全に音声で会話します。
Then why is this account a very good computer, because every word of it is in front of IBM
では、なぜこのアカウントが非常に優れたコンピューターであるのかというと、そのすべての単語が IBM の前にあるからです。
That is to say, he deliberately regarded IBM as the best computer, and every letter of HAL is one in front of IBM.
つまり、彼は意図的に IBM を最高のコンピュータとみなしており、HAL のすべての文字が IBM の前にあるのです。
So he was in front of IBM, and behind that there was an AI artificial intelligence in 2001, and many people have seen it
つまり、彼はIBMの前にいて、その後ろには2001年にAI人工知能があり、多くの人がそれを見たことがある
This is the first robot that knows what love is, so his love is quite scary, that is to say, in unconditional
これは愛が何であるかを知った最初のロボットなので、彼の愛は非常に恐ろしいものです、つまり無条件​​で
so by the end his mother was freaking out
それで最後には彼の母親はおかしくなった
2004 Public Enemy of Robots, which means that every house has 3 to 5 robots to do all the house cleaning
2004 年「ロボットの公共の敵」。これは、すべての家に 3 ～ 5 台のロボットがあり、家の掃除をすべて行うことを意味します。
Later, the robot was disobedient and had some problems.
その後、ロボットは従わなくなり、いくつかの問題が発生しました。
Piano player in the cloud 2013
クラウド上のピアノ演奏者 2013
this person is totally lonely
この人は完全に孤独だ
He completely uses this text message
彼はこのテキストメッセージを完全に使用しています
Chatting with another invisible person
見えない別の人とチャットする
a woman
女性
that's called semansa
それはセマンサと呼ばれます
After talking, he really felt that he loved him very much.
話した後、彼は本当に自分のことを愛していると感じました。
But he once asked him a question
しかし、彼は一度質問したことがあります
He said how many people are you dating at the same time
彼はあなたが同時に何人と付き合っているのかと言いました
He said 365
彼は365と言った
Also this terrible thing
こんなひどいことも
So the comprehensive plan for 2014
それで、2014年の総合計画は
That means this is a scientist played by Johnny Depp
つまり、これはジョニー・デップが演じる科学者です
Then at this time he can continue his life
そうすれば、現時点では彼は人生を続けることができます
this is a new idea
これは新しいアイデアです
Then let me talk about it now
それなら今から話しましょう
AlphaGo and Natural Language Understanding
AlphaGo と自然言語理解
These two discrepancies correspond to natural language for machines
これら 2 つの矛盾は、機械の自然言語に対応します。
responsible for far more than the period
期間をはるかに超えた責任を負う
Because there are many self-evident common sense
自明の常識がたくさんあるから
derived or derived knowledge
派生した、または派生した知識
For example, before you get off work today
たとえば、今日仕事を終える前に
In Line, your wife sent a message saying
奥様からLINEでこんなメッセージが届きました。
no cooking tonight
今夜は料理はありません
what does that mean
どういう意味ですか
there are two
二つあります
one for learning and one for excellence
1 つは学習用、もう 1 つは卓越性用
it's good to say
言うのは良いことです
Two can go out and find a good
二人で出かけて良いものを見つけよう
delicious restaurant, right?
おいしいレストランですよね？
The other one is to say what are you doing around here today?
もう一つは、今日ここで何をしているのですか？
forgot something so he doesn't cook
何かを忘れたので彼は料理をしません
then this thing
それからこのこと
It is a bit difficult for a machine to understand
機械にはちょっとわかりにくいですが
Language understanding is often associated with larger contacts
言語理解は多くの場合、より大きな接触に関連しています
So this contact is
したがって、この連絡先は
The environment in which he spoke today
今日彼が話した環境
Like what's the news today
今日のニュースは何だったみたいに
A lot of these things are contact
これらの多くは接触です
how do you know where he is from
彼の出身地をどうやって知っていますか
Get some Message written by
によって書かれたメッセージを取得する
The relatively simple rules for the term
この用語の比較的単純なルール
The rule is that you surround each other
ルールはお互いを囲むことです
Then he dies with only one eye left
そして片目だけを残して死ぬ
die with only one eye left
片目だけ残して死ぬ
Now all artificial intelligence
今ではすべての人工知能が
can go to see
見に行くことができます
our video today
今日の私たちのビデオ
How about thank you all
みなさんに感謝してみてはどうでしょうか
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
Everything that is done on this is a single
この上で行われることはすべて単一です
objective optimization
目的の最適化
like the goal of surrounding him is to win
彼を囲む目的は勝つことであるかのように
So he put a lot of chessboards down
それで彼はたくさんのチェス盤を置いた
The end result is win or lose
最終的な結果は勝つか負けるかです
make this the last goal
これを最後の目標にする
Now this deep learning is very well trained in this area
現在、この深層学習はこの分野で非常によく訓練されています
He can even play with himself
彼は自分自身でも遊ぶことができます
He can memorize the result when he wins or loses at the end
彼は最後に勝ったり負けたりしたときに結果を記憶できる
Then do a lot of interesting analysis below
次に、以下で多くの興味深い分析を行ってください
The earliest computer worker Turin
最古のコンピューター労働者トリノ
It's a pity to live to be 42 years old
42歳まで生きるのは残念だ
He thought of a test
彼はテストを考えた
Is it a machine or a human?
それは機械ですか、それとも人間ですか?
Do you have the ability to approach people?
人に近づく力はありますか？
A simple test he did
彼が行った簡単なテスト
Just put a tester in the first room
最初の部屋にテスターを置くだけ
one person
一人
Put two computers in the second room
2 番目の部屋に 2 台のコンピューターを置く
one is real
1つは本物です
is also a terminal
端末でもあります
you can message him
彼にメッセージを送ることができます
A machine is a piece of software
マシンはソフトウェアの一部です
So if the person on the left
つまり、左側の人であれば、
he can't tell
彼は言えません
he can give him 30 minutes
彼は30分時間をくれるだろう
If he can't tell which one is the machine
どれが機械なのか見分けがつかない場合
which one is human
どっちが人間だ
that machine is successful
そのマシンは成功しました
so he said this
それで彼はこう言いました
what is understanding
理解とは何ですか
is the last
最後です
You can't tell if he's a human or a machine
彼が人間なのか機械なのか見分けがつかない
So AI research
そこでAIの研究
Heart failure ups and downs are very many times
心不全の浮き沈みは非常に多い
This is a
これは
Norville Economist
ノービルのエコノミスト
winner of economics
経済学の勝者
Herb assignment famous
ハーブの割り当てが有名
at Connected Manor
コネクテッドマナーにて
他說Machine will be capable within 20 years
他說Machine will be capable within 20 years
of doing any work a man can do
人間ができるあらゆる仕事をすること
This was spoken in 1965
これは1965年に話されたものです
1985 is about to happen
1985年が近づいています
everyone knows no
誰もがノーを知っています
AI rehearsals are in
AIリハーサル中
Scholars at MIT
MITの学者
Marvin Minsky
マービン・ミンスキー
two years after him in 1967
彼の2年後の1967年
He said within a generation
彼は一世代以内にこう言った
the problem of creating artificial intelligence
人工知能の作成の問題
was substantially be solved
実質的に解決されました
So because of these people's
だから、この人たちのせいで
So a lot of research funding is thrown away
多額の研究資金が無駄に浪費される
But the effect is very limited
しかしその効果は非常に限られている
So let's look at some examples of failure
それでは、いくつかの失敗例を見てみましょう
This is of course more expensive.
もちろん、これはより高価です。
so i put it here
だからここに置きました
Japan's fifth-generation computer in 1982
1982年に誕生した日本の第5世代コンピュータ
At that time, Japan's national power was very strong.
当時、日本の国力は非常に強かった。
they have a lot of money
彼らはたくさんのお金を持っています
so what
だから何
He wanted to create a computer that was fast and could understand people
彼は高速で人間を理解できるコンピューターを作りたかったのです
The result is nothing
結果は何もない
Let it go
手放す
This Japanese compares
この日本人は比べます
He is inside
彼は中にいます
for being quick to admit mistakes
間違いをすぐに認めるから
But he doesn't want to admit his mistakes
しかし彼は自分の間違いを認めたくない
so how do we know
では、どうやって知ることができるのでしょうか
because he made a famous
彼は有名になったから
so-called battery point
いわゆるバッテリーポイント
He thinks this electronic pool point is all-encompassing
彼は、この電子プールポイントは包括的であると考えています
can solve many human problems
人間の多くの問題を解決できる
when he finally finished
彼がついに終わったとき
This electronic battery point
この電子バッテリーポイント
He would have sold millions
彼なら何百万も売れただろう
Later, you can buy it for 10,000 Taiwan dollars
その後、10,000台湾ドルで購入できます
It's basically called a jump price
基本的にはジャンププライスと呼ばれます
no one wants
誰も望んでいない
Another CYC Project is also a
もう一つのCYCプロジェクトも
very famous 1984
非常に有名な1984年
there is a very
とてもあります
He wants to collect a lot of try
彼はたくさんのトライを集めたいと思っている
Then the computer can think like a human in the future
そうすれば、将来コンピュータは人間のように考えることができるようになる
He tried to use logic to choose
彼は論理を使って選択しようとした
because at that time logic was what they used most
当時彼らが最もよく使っていたのはロジックだったからです
But this project later because there is no specific application
ただし、このプロジェクトは具体的なアプリケーションがないため、後ほど
while daytime demonstrations
昼間のデモ中
he still exists
彼はまだ存在します
But you can also go to license
ただし、ライセンスを取得することもできます
But very few people use it
でもそれを使っている人はほとんどいない
Because they never thought about how to use my knowledge
彼らは私の知識をどのように活用するか考えたこともなかったので、
so it's a pity
だから残念だ
And this one is full...
そしてこちらも満席・・・
Japan's entrance examination robots set their goals in 2014
日本の入試ロボットは2014年に目標を設定
To be admitted to the University of Tokyo
東京大学に入学するために
Just like our entrance exam
私たちの入学試験と同じように
We have about five or six subjects
科目は5つか6つくらいあります
Each subject will give you textbook reference books
各科目には教科書の参考書が与えられます
Or some related news?
それとも関連ニュース？
You can go to the exam like a human
人間のように試験に臨むことができます
Then this thing is not only made in Japan
そうすると、これは日本製だけではありません
Mainland China spent 20 billion yuan
中国本土は200億元を費やした
about two years ago
約2年前
voted two or three years ago
2、3年前に投票した
20 billion, let's not talk about RMB
200億、人民元の話はやめましょう
Our NT$20 billion
当社の200億台湾ドル
20 billion also happened from there
200億もそこから起こりました
he's just in this one
彼はちょうどこの中にいます
Robots 20 billion yuan was spent on exam robots
ロボット 試験ロボットに200億元が費やされた
for about a dozen schools
約十数の学校で
They hope that within three to five years
彼らは3年から5年以内にそうなることを望んでいます
This time the Japanese are more honest
今度は日本人がもっと正直になった
he gave up last year
彼は去年諦めた
because they found
彼らが見つけたから
Now the score is about the middle and lower grades
今では中学・低学年くらいのスコアです
I just can't get into that public university
あの国公立大学には入れない
Probably private universities can be admitted
おそらく私立大学も入学できるでしょう
but the computer you need to know
知っておくべきコンピューター
he is very rambunctious
他非常賴皮
because he never forgets
彼は決して忘れないから
all historical geography
すべての歴史的地理
remember everything clearly
すべてをはっきりと覚えている
so you test him
だからあなたは彼を試します
But there is one thing he must lose
しかし、彼には失くしなければならないものが一つある
But his current method is difficult to break through
しかし彼の現在のやり方を突破するのは難しい
so he thinks
それで彼は考えます
this is probably hopeless
これはおそらく絶望的だ
the successful case
成功したケース
It's all this commercial company
それはすべてこの営利企業です
IBM Sunland beats the king of western gas
IBMサンランドが西部ガス王を破る
At that time they were
当時彼らは、
It is assumed that this game of Go may be 50 years later
この囲碁は50年後であると推測されている
will defeat
負けるだろう
Because the maintenance complexity may be tens of millions of times
メンテナンスの複雑さは数千万倍になる可能性があるため
That IBM Watson Beats the Jeopardy Champion
IBM Watson が危険のチャンピオンに勝つ
Jeopardy is a simple question answering system
Jeopardy はシンプルな質問応答システムです
so he might ask if you are the winner of the physics prize in 1998
それで彼はあなたが 1998 年の物理学賞の受賞者かどうか尋ねるかもしれません
Who is it? Questions like this
誰ですか? このような質問
That's about speed
それはスピードの問題です
so the computer
それでコンピューター
We all thought he was voice input at first
最初は誰もが彼が音声入力だと思っていました
then just like people
それなら人と同じように
actually not
実際にはそうではありません
Later he was rambunctious
その後彼は暴れだした
He means the examiner
彼は試験官を意味します
It's the show host
番組の司会者です
when starting to read the topic
トピックを読み始めるとき
He just presses a key to put the text
キーを押すだけでテキストを入力できます
Already written text questions
すでに書かれたテキストの質問
send to computer
コンピュータに送信する
So the computer has five or six seconds
したがって、コンピュータには 5 ～ 6 秒かかります
He can calculate while reciting the title
タイトルを唱えながら計算できる
In this case he will press the button
この場合、彼はボタンを押します
will be faster than people
人よりも早くなるだろう
So this is a bit unreasonable
だからこれはちょっと無理がある
The way IBM wins
IBMが勝つ方法
actually
実際
really a big project
本当に大きなプロジェクト
He spent 25 engineer
彼はエンジニアに25ドルを費やした
are very advanced
非常に先進的です
IBM engineer
IBMのエンジニア
five years
五年的時間
plus there is
さらにあります
Many schools cooperate with him
多くの学校が彼に協力している
Then what
じゃあ何
every question asked
あらゆる質問が
He'll have 100 different systems
彼は 100 の異なるシステムを持っているでしょう
to come up with an answer
答えを見つけるために
some systems
いくつかのシステム
It is the kind of confidence that is relatively high
比較的信頼度が高い種類のものです
Some systems are lower
一部のシステムはこれより低い
he will just vote
彼はただ投票するだけだ
He'll find out the answer
彼は答えを見つけるだろう
he didn't use
彼は使わなかった
the way we call understanding
私たちが理解と呼ぶ方法
naa fago
ナァ・ファーゴ
This is really quite powerful
これは本当にかなり強力です
Google AFAGO
Google アファゴ
It's not Google's own
Google 独自のものではありません
Also bought the one from the UK
こちらもイギリスから購入しました
a company
会社
Then Google and do it again
それからGoogleでもう一度やってください
beat korean flag
韓国の国旗を破る
Go back to Banner King
バナーキングに戻る
deep learning
ディープラーニング
this is part
これは一部です
and many other tricks
その他多くのトリック
But the way he and humans set the flag
しかし、彼と人間が旗を立てる方法
very different
大不相同
all of us
私たち全員
Teacher Xu Zhansheng
徐振生先生
He is making a banner
彼はバナーを作っています
Then he every week
それから彼は毎週
will invite a Xiangqi Master
Xiangqiマスターを招待します
come talk to him for an hour
彼と1時間話しに来てください
I use my old man to purchase
私はおじさんを使って購入します
this
これ
He said every flag of the master
彼はマスターのすべての旗を言った
considering
検討中
Two or three possible moves, why so few
可能な手は 2 ～ 3 つ、なぜこんなに少ないのか
That is to say, when ordinary people play chess
つまり、普通の人がチェスをするとき、
90% impossible to win the paper
論文に勝つのは90％不可能
you don't even think about it
あなたはそれについてさえ考えていません
just don't watch at all
ただ全く見ないでください
But the master is 99%
でもマスターは99％
Even 99.9% he won't consider
99.9%でも考慮しないだろう
so you can see in
で見ることができます
Some parks have a really good camera operator
いくつかの公園には本当に優秀なカメラマンがいます
He can play with 10 people at the same time
同時に10人でプレイできる
He walked to the second place after he got off.
彼は降りてから二番目の場所まで歩いた。
Just get off the chair and walk back like this
椅子から降りて、このように歩いて戻ります
The first one hasn't been downloaded yet
最初のものはまだダウンロードされていません
It means only thinking about the actual species every time
それは常に実際の種についてのみ考えることを意味します
Because you want to think about where the other party might go next
相手が次にどこへ行くかを考えたいから
So there are quite a few steps here and there.
したがって、あちこちにかなりの手順があります。
So in this case you consider two or three possibilities
したがって、この場合は 2 つまたは 3 つの可能性を考慮します。
You can't remember all this in your head
これらすべてを頭の中で思い出すことはできません
So the great thing is
それで素晴らしいのは
These masters with such a small head
こんなに頭の小さいマスターたち
Calculations are so slow and memory is so poor
計算が遅いし記憶力も悪い
How could he be in such a fast time
どうして彼はこんなに早くいられるんだろう
Just finish thinking about this actual possibility
この実際の可能性について考えるのはやめてください
Many untimely directions have been automatically deleted in the previous life
多くの時機を逸した指示は前世で自動的に削除されています
Our feeling is that the result of his talk with the master is that someone actually memorized a lot of patterns
私たちの感覚では、彼がマスターと話した結果、誰かが実際に多くのパターンを記憶したということです
like you say it like so many of your old photos
あなたが言うように、あなたの古い写真の多くのように
You don't remember very clearly, but you know where you have been and what movies you have been looking for
あまりはっきりとは覚えていませんが、どこに行ったのか、どんな映画を探していたのかは知っています。
There is a similar experience in the next issue
次号にも同様の体験があります
After downloading, he will have many such patterns left behind.
ダウンロード後、そのようなパターンが多数残ることになります。
These patterns can help him do a quick search
これらのパターンは、迅速な検索に役立ちます
I told Mr. Xu Zhuansheng that now Afagou has won against Weiqi
私は徐伝生氏に、アファゴウがウェイチーに勝ったと伝えました。
It's Master Vicky, what research can you do now?
マスター・ヴィッキーです、今からどんな研究ができるでしょうか？
He said that in fact, in their direction
実際、彼らの方向に向かって、彼はこう言いました。
This is the current Deep Learning, it is impossible for AFAGO to do it
これは今のディープラーニングです、AFAGOには無理です
That is to say, how computers can help people improve, you will scare others
つまり、コンピュータが人々の向上にどのように役立つかということは、他の人を怖がらせることになるということです
like my pool coach is doing too
私のプールコーチもやってるみたいに
You said the world champion pool must be very good
世界チャンピオンの卓球はとても上手いに違いないと君は言った
If we saw him, we would lose confidence
もし彼を見たら、私たちは自信を失うでしょう
Exercising is boring, it's not like that
運動はつまらない、そんなことはない
I hope that you can make more progress at your current level
今のレベルでさらに上達できることを願っています
so you want a coach
それでコーチが欲しいのですか
Then this computer plays chess
それからこのコンピュータはチェスをします
he can't teach you
彼はあなたに教えることができません
He can't explain why he won
彼はなぜ勝ったのか説明できない
So this is actually very little help to us.
したがって、これは実際には私たちにとってほとんど役に立ちません。
What we need is actually a game that is more like a human playing chess.
私たちが実際に必要としているのは、人間がチェスをしているのにもっと似たゲームです。
I'll tell you what's wrong with this step.
このステップの何が問題なのかを説明します。
see it right away
すぐに見てください
Such a study is actually relevant to the current
このような研究は実際に現在に関連しています
All machine learning is Machine Impossible
すべての機械学習は機械では不可能です
at least now i can see that
少なくとも今はそれがわかります
OK, let me show you a simple
OK、簡単なものをお見せしましょう
empathetic robot
共感ロボット
What does it mean to have everything but ventilation
換気以外のすべてを備えているとはどういう意味ですか?
Here's this sparring system for billiards
こちらはビリヤード用のスパーリングシステムです
Just opposite here is a computer robot
ちょうど向かい側にはコンピューターロボットがいます
Then you see how good he is
そうすれば彼がどれほど優れているかがわかります
The oil of this machine is its ability, right?
このマシンのオイルは能力ですよね？
nothing can kill
何も殺すことはできない
I just wanted to say that if he could teach me
彼が教えてくれれば、と言いたかっただけです
Then the coach is out of work, right?
じゃあコーチは失業中ですよね？
What does it mean that this computer owes Dongfeng now?
このコンピュータが現在東風に借りがあるということは何を意味しますか?
He doesn't know, he doesn't understand my shortcomings
彼は知らない、私の欠点を理解していない
then what
じゃあ何
He has no so-called strategy concept now
彼にはいわゆる戦略概念が今はありません
that he wants to win
彼は勝ちたいと思っている
Of course it's too easy for him to beat me now
もちろん、今彼が私を倒すのは簡単すぎる
Just because I can't even kill him
ただ彼を殺すことすらできないから
But what he wants to teach me is to
でも彼が私に教えたいのは、
The meaning of being kind
親切であることの意味
where is my shortcoming
私の欠点はどこですか
He told me how your knowledge changed
彼はあなたの知識がどのように変わったかを教えてくれました
you can fight whatever you want
あなたは好きなように戦うことができます
can't do it
それはできません
So language understanding is generally regarded as the highest level of intelligence
したがって、言語理解は一般に最高レベルの知能とみなされています
When the robot arrives, if the language ability can be strengthened
ロボットが来たら言語能力を強化できれば
Become better at communicating and directing
コミュニケーションと指示が上手になる
There are more places that can help manpower
人材を助けてくれる場所は他にもある
like internet of things
モノのインターネットのような
The Internet of Things is actually connecting all the things in the home to the Internet.
モノのインターネットとは、実際には家にあるすべてのものをインターネットに接続できることです
can be strung together
一緒につなぐことができます
There is also a mark on the milk in the refrigerator
冷蔵庫の牛乳にも跡がついています
It can know when to buy new milk
新しい牛乳をいつ購入するかを知ることができる
What kind of fruit is also on each of them
それぞれにはどんな果物が乗っているのでしょう
Sports and leisure
スポーツとレジャー
The exercise we just talked about
先ほど話した演習
This table tennis might be the fastest
この卓球が一番速いかもしれない
you want to play tennis
テニスをしたいですか
You don't play with machines at all
あなたはまったく機械で遊ばない
Word processing for slow formulas
遅い数式のワードプロセッサ
This is the future administrative secretary should be careful
これは将来の行政長官が注意すべきことです
just a lot of work
ただたくさんの仕事
Not everything it does can be replaced by a computer
すべての機能がコンピューターに置き換えられるわけではありません
It means that 80% can replace
80％が代替できるということです
Now there is only one secretary, it only needs to handle the remaining 20%
現在、秘書は 1 人だけなので、残りの 20% を処理するだけで済みます。
So this is a terrible environment
だから、ここはひどい環境なんです
Natural language understanding, let me briefly tell you about it now
自然言語理解、今から簡単にお話します
It is of course my personal opinion that it needs to be bumpy inside
内部に必要な粗さはもちろん私の個人的な意見です
If you do learn natural language, we have a colleague here
自然言語を学習している場合は、ここに同僚がいます
I probably won't be too convinced after hearing it.
それを聞いてもあまり納得できないかもしれません。
natural language concepts
自然言語の概念
In fact, the concept of natural language is quite vague
実際、自然言語の概念は非常に曖昧です
and it's hard to define
そして定義するのは難しい
Like I said Fascinating Article, right?
先ほども言ったように、魅力的な記事ですよね?
This is Fascinating to me
これは私にとって魅力的です
what you see may be different
見えるものは違うかもしれない
A good way to do it, what does that mean?
良い方法ですが、それは何を意味しますか？
A good tennis player
優れたテニス選手
This one is more confusing that is
これはもっと混乱します
Everyone's ability to play tennis is different
テニスの能力は人それぞれ異なります
So I say good, maybe others say it is very common
だから私は良いと言う、多分他の人はそれが非常に一般的だと言うでしょう
So these words, but we usually speak like this
この言葉ですが、私たちは普段こんな風に話します
Do you understand?
わかりますか？
A good student
優秀な生徒
Then you know what it means, right?
それならそれが何を意味するかわかりますよね？
However, what does it mean to be unwavering
でも、揺るぎないってどういうことだろう
The honest method, the method is actually very difficult
正直な方法、その方法は実はとても難しいのです
Because have you ever read "Mingfa", "Xingfa" or something?
だって、「ミンファ」とか「シンファ」とか読んだことがありますか？
A dozen pairs of what corporate law
何十組の会社法
you haven't read it, how did you suffer
読んでいないのですが、どう感じますか？
So, wait a minute, let's talk about
それで、ちょっと待って、次のことを話しましょう
what these things how we run in the world
これらは何ですか、私たちは世界でどうやって走るのですか
good student
良い学生
Let's mention that these concepts have their context
これらの概念にはコンテキストがあることに注意してください。
background, the background of this conversation and this context
背景、この会話の背景、およびこのコンテキスト
allows you to bring this convergence
この収束を可能にします
So if you talk to someone who can't stand it at the train station
だから駅で我慢できない人に話しかけたら
Kaohsiung, Taipei, then he will immediately
高雄、台北ならすぐに行きます
I almost ask you what time it will be over
何時に終わるのか聞いてしまいそうになる
You usually don't understand what you say
普通は自分の言っていることが理解できない
Therefore, understanding different levels is actually related to many
したがって、さまざまなレベルを理解することは、実際には多くのことに関連しています。
The question answering system thing is very similar
質問応答システムもよく似ています
some questions may be easy to answer
いくつかの質問は簡単に答えられるかもしれません
Answers to some questions may be equivalent to a doctoral or master's thesis
一部の質問への回答は博士論文または修士論文に相当する場合があります
So understanding is the same, some are easy, some are very easy
つまり、理解することは同じであり、簡単なものもあれば、非常に簡単なものもある
What we are interested in today is to talk about the understanding ability required by service robots
今日はサービスロボットに求められる理解力についてお話したいと思います
basically he needs to be able to take basic instructions
基本的に彼は基本的な指示を受けることができる必要があります
Then you can have a conversation, it's not easy if you can have a conversation
そうすれば会話ができる、会話するのは簡単ではない
like when we often ask questions
よく質問するときのように
Because I went to the bank to ask questions
銀行に聞きに行ったので
don't understand their terminology
彼らの用語が理解できません
so i talked for a long time
それで長い間話しました
Well, if he is a pilot, he can understand
まあ、パイロットなら分かるだろうけど
He just turned it into saying that you want to deposit a fixed deposit, right?
定期預金を預けたいと言い出しただけですよね？
We didn't know the word fixed deposit, so we talked for a long time
私たちは定期預金という言葉を知らなかったので、長い間話しました
the same goes for robots
ロボットも同様です
today you ask a question
今日あなたは質問します
Can he narrow down the scope of his problem quickly?
彼は問題の範囲をすぐに絞り込むことができるでしょうか?
It's better to give suggestions
提案したほうがいいよ
say like my wife
私の妻のように言う
his students often
彼の生徒たちはよく
I ask him how to do everything
私は彼にすべてのやり方を尋ねます
Then he told him that he would run to that city
それから彼はその街まで走ると言いました
to be able to make suggestions
提案ができるようになる
This robot can replace that student
このロボットはあの生徒の代わりをすることができます
What many of our master students do now
修士課程の学生の多くが現在行っていること
To be honest, it can really be replaced in the future
正直に言うと、将来的には置き換えられる可能性があります
Do you want to study for a doctorate in the future, or don't study for a master's degree
将来博士号を取得するために勉強したいですか、それとも修士号を取得するために勉強しませんか
computing words words
単語を計算する
we think
我々が考えます
Computing is to calculate this thing, which seems to be done by a person who is good at mathematics.
これを計算するのがコンピューティングで、数学が得意な人がやるそうです。
But if you look carefully at the following questions, you will find that everyone can do it and very quickly
しかし、次の質問を注意深く見てみると、誰でもすぐに実行できることがわかります。
why is this
どうしてこれなの
May I ask what is the floating rate of the second-year fixed deposit in US dollars?
2 年目の定期預金の変動金利は米ドルでいくらですか?
This is very clear, right?
これは非常に明白ですよね？
Immediately take out this watch from the computer
すぐにこの時計をコンピュータから取り出してください
Two-year float rate here 1.15
2年変動金利は1.15
If he says one less
彼が一つ少ないと言ったら
May I ask what is the interest rate of the second-year fixed deposit in US dollars?
米ドル建ての2年目の定期預金の金利はいくらですか？
The customer service will immediately ask him whether the power rate is fixed or floating
顧客サービスはすぐに電力料金が固定か変動かを尋ねます。
How hard is it for a computer to do this today
今日、コンピューターがこれを行うのはどれだけ難しいか
Or what is the floating rate of the US dollar fixed deposit?
あるいは米ドル定期預金の変動金利とは何ですか？
This seldom-speaking second grader will immediately ask back how many months
めったに話さないこの 2 年生は、すぐに「何ヶ月」と聞き返します。
So today if you say
それで今日、あなたが言うなら
I want to replace this customer service, as long as I can answer these questions like him
私も彼と同じようにこれらの質問に答えられる限り、このカスタマー サービスを置き換えたいと思っています
Make up for what is missing
足りないものを補う
Then why did he know there would be a shortage of these things?
では、なぜ彼はこれらのものが不足するとわかったのでしょうか?
So in fact when you're talking
実際に話しているとき
Are you talking about a constraint
制約のことを言ってるの？
Then there is a deficiency in this condition, and he will know it immediately
そうすれば、この状態には欠陥があり、彼はすぐにそれを知るでしょう
This man is very powerful
この人はとても力強い人だ
Then you may ask why you can’t talk about the following
それでは、なぜ次のことについて話せないのかと疑問に思うかもしれません。
What are the benefits of a two-year floating time deposit in US dollars?
米ドル建ての 2 年変動定期預金にはどのようなメリットがありますか?
Sounds weird that the float runs here
ここにフロートが走っているのは奇妙に思えます
because every word he has his best friend
なぜなら、彼の言葉一つ一つに彼の親友がいるからです
with less good friends, less familiar friends
それほど仲の良い友達、あまり親しくない友達と
when you go to sit at a table outside
外のテーブルに座ろうとすると
You'll find that your best friend is sitting next to you
あなたの親友があなたの隣に座っていることに気づくでしょう
This float is the best friend of interest rates
この浮動株は金利の強い味方です
he can't sit next to the sophomore
彼は二年生の隣に座ることができない
then we are on the computer
それから私たちはコンピューター上にいます
In fact, all these things can be calculated
実際、これらすべては計算可能です
which things are close to which things
どの物がどの物に近いか
Sometimes order is very important, this is the order just mentioned
場合によっては順序が非常に重要です。これは先ほど述べた順序です
jokes from my time
私の時代のジョーク
Most of you probably haven't heard of it
おそらくほとんどの人は聞いたことがないでしょう
there is a foreigner
外国人がいます
Americans learn English
アメリカ人は英語を学ぶ
No, he learned Chinese and came to Taiwan
いいえ、彼は中国語を勉強して台湾に来ました。
when he got off the plane
彼が飛行機から降りたとき
he will be a little bit
彼は少しはなるだろう
he just wants to show off
彼はただ自慢したいだけです
the girl who came to pick up the plane
飛行機を迎えに来た女の子
looks very beautiful
とても美しく見えます
he tensed up
他一下緊張
he said against
彼は反対した
he was going to talk about you
彼はあなたのことを話すつもりだった
just the other way around
ちょうどその逆
hello mom
こんにちはママ
The girl froze for a moment
少女は一瞬固まった
do not understand at all
全く分かりません
Then he didn't see it right
それから彼はそれを正しく見ませんでした
he just thinks about it
彼はただそれについて考えている
He wants to usually say hello to your mother
彼はいつもあなたのお母さんに挨拶したいと思っています
the girl
女の子
just smiled a little
少しだけ微笑んだ
still pretty embarrassing
まだかなり恥ずかしい
This man is still wrong
この人はまだ間違っている
So in the end he figured it must be right
それで最終的に彼はそれが正しいに違いないと考えた
hello mom
こんにちはママ
So this is such a simple sequence
これは非常に単純なシーケンスです
when you usually talk
普段話しているとき
Didn't think about it, didn't think about it, right?
考えてなかった、考えてなかったですよね？
just say it
ただ言ってください
that's why
それが理由です
very interesting
とても興味深い
so you
だからあなたは
must be seen as a language constraint
言語の制約と見なす必要がある
In fact, the language has many restrictions
実際、この言語には多くの制限があります
then why do we know how to say
では、なぜ私たちはこう言うことができるのでしょうか？
In fact, we have a lot of panels in our minds
実際、私たちの頭の中にはたくさんのパネルがあります
You don't even have to think about it to generate these automatically
これらを自動的に生成するため、考える必要さえありません。
will automatically understand what others say
他人の言うことを自動的に理解するようになる
so today we
だから今日私たちは
At least the model I made is to learn these Panels
少なくとも私が作ったモデルはこれらのパネルを学ぶことです
What about the two-year fixed deposit interest rate in US dollars we asked just now?
先ほど質問した米ドル建ての2年定期預金金利はどうでしょうか。
what those things
それらのことは何ですか
It's a condition
それは条件です
If you don’t make sense, the conditions are met
意味がわからなければ条件は満たしている
If you don’t make sense, you still have some conditions
意味が分からない場合でも、いくつかの条件があります
ok
Ok
If your language skills are not good enough
語学力が十分ではない場合
Like the English we just arrived in the United States
アメリカに来たばかりのイギリス人のように
understand every word
すべての言葉を理解する
But I don't understand that sentence
でもその文は分かりません
It means what is the condition
どういう状態なのかというと、
what is the meaning of its whole condition
その状態全体の意味は何ですか
have no idea
全く分かりません
So elementary school math wheel word problem
小学校の算数ホイールの文章問題
It's a very simple quiz
とても簡単なクイズです
We're doing language analysis inside
内部では言語分析を行っています
this is all inside
これはすべて内側にあります
The so-called least attempted program in elementary school
小学校におけるいわゆる最も挑戦されていないプログラム
Everyone knows that computers are now doing these problems
コンピュータがこうした問題を抱えていることは誰もが知っています。
to what extent
どの程度まで
Recently at MIT they used machine learning to do this
最近MITでは機械学習を使ってこれを行いました
Average 50 points
平均50点
Even the one who looks like a child will probably get 50 points in the test
見た目は子供でもテストで50点は取れるだろう
get spanked at home
家で叩かれる
It's just that there is no child who is worse than him in the exam
ただ、試験で彼より悪い子はいない
This sounds simple to us
これは私たちには簡単に聞こえます
Xiaomi has two apples
Xiaomiにはリンゴが2つある
30 kilometers cut two
30キロ2切り
His difficulty is
彼の困難は
He did not sharpen two pencils
彼は鉛筆を2本削りませんでした
fill it in yourself
自分で埋めてください
ate an apple
リンゴを食べた
How many apples does Xiaomi have?
Xiaomi にはリンゴが何個ありますか?
Computers are now equally difficult
コンピューターも今では同じくらい難しい
After reading this, he doesn't know what you are doing
これを読んだ後、彼はあなたが何をしているのか分かりません
Xiaohua's father is thirty years older than him
シャオファの父親は彼より30歳年上である
in two years
2年
His dad is twice his age
彼のお父さんは彼の年齢の2倍です
How old is Xiao Hua now?
シャオ・ファは今何歳ですか？
It's all a constitutional condition
それはすべて憲法上の条件です
So understand quickly
だから早く理解して
So the reason why they won't do it
それで彼らがそれをしない理由は
But because I don't understand this reason
でもこの理由が分からないので
Then we asked about restaurant tea science, like Siri actually has restaurant tea science,
次に、Siri が実際にレストランの紅茶の科学を持っているように、レストランの紅茶の科学について尋ねました。
We are looking for a meal, what can we get next to the Sun Yat-Sen Memorial Hall,
食事を探していますが、国父記念館の隣で何が食べられるでしょうか。
You don't need to ask him, and now you can't,
彼に尋ねる必要はありませんし、今はそれができません。
That is to say, he can only do voice translation for you now,
つまり、彼は今のところ音声翻訳しかできません。
The question is too complicated to answer, that is, he can't make sense,
その質問は複雑すぎて答えることができません、つまり、彼は意味を理解できません。
He doesn't know whether the conditions for your speech are met or what you want to do,
彼はあなたのスピーチの条件が満たされているかどうか、あなたが何をしたいのかを知りません。
So just input these conditions into the computer,
これらの条件をコンピュータに入力するだけです。
Computers can answer more things,
コンピュータはより多くのことに答えることができますが、
Serial drama this is Cliff Hanger,
連続ドラマ「こちらクリフハンガー」
That is to say, the suspense we just mentioned is the condition of a sentence,
つまり、先ほど述べたサスペンスは文の条件であり、
You can talk about a story, and a story also has its beginnings and transitions,
ストーリーについて話すことはできますが、ストーリーにも始まり、成功、変遷があります。
In the end, what does the so-called successful conclusion of this story mean?
結局のところ、この物語のいわゆる成功した結末は何を意味するのでしょうか？
Even if this person is not married, did that person have a successful relationship in the end?
たとえこの人が結婚していなかったとしても、その人は最終的にうまくいった関係を築いたのでしょうか？
these things
これらの事
Cliff Hanger is actually a fulfillment condition,
実はクリフハンガーが達成条件なのですが、
Originally, he acted in ten episodes of the American series,
当初、彼はアメリカのシリーズの10のエピソードに出演していましたが、
Taiwan can play 40 episodes,
台湾では40のエピソードを再生できます。
He hangs there all the time, and he can add a lot of encryption
彼はいつもそこにハングアップしており、多くの暗号化を追加できます
So, computing with words is a very interesting
つまり、言葉を使った計算は非常に興味深いのです。
That is, you didn’t just say that there is only one sentence, your story also has an ending
つまり、一文だけじゃなくて、物語には結末があるということ
How do you find out this ending
この結末をどうやって知ることができますか？
So if you think about it carefully
それでよく考えてみると
Every sentence we see on the Internet is make sense
インターネット上で目にするすべての文章には意味があります
Most people need to make sense when speaking
ほとんどの人は話すときに意味を理解する必要があります
So he has some restrictions
だから彼にはいくつかの制限がある
But the literary exception
しかし文学的な例外は
Why is literature an exception
なぜ文学は例外なのか
what do you say i'm in a
私がいるって何て言うの？
cool night
涼しい夜
Walk alone on the beach hill
浜辺の丘を一人で歩く
Thinking of yesterday's banquet
昨日の宴会を思い出して
There's a lot of this kind of talk that doesn't serve any purpose
こういう何の役にも立たない話が多い
let's not talk now
今は話さないようにしましょう
Today we are talking about service machinery people
今日はサービス機械担当者について話します
Including carpet cleaning
カーペットクリーニングも含めて
clean the sofa
ソファを掃除する
This is a very clear instruction
これは非常に明確な指示です
or turn on the air conditioner
またはエアコンをつけます
So these conditions are actually the so-called knowledge
つまり、これらの条件は実際にはいわゆる知識です
If you have this knowledge you will have a way to understand and then you can answer
この知識があれば、理解する方法があり、答えられるでしょう
Then why is it like the two edges of a calendar sword
ではなぜそれは暦の剣の両刃のようなものなのでしょうか
because you have this knowledge structure
この知識構造があるからです
So when you're dealing with a very complex problem
したがって、非常に複雑な問題に対処しているときは、
a very complicated sentence you can understand very quickly
非常に複雑な文をすぐに理解できる
But it also limits human thinking
しかしそれは人間の思考を制限するものでもあります
This is when we do research
これは私たちが研究をするときです
why do you sometimes jump out
なぜ時々飛び出すのですか
Go to a third party to see why you are doing the right thing
サードパーティに行って、なぜ自分が正しいことをしているのかを確認してください
For example, the doctor's concept of health is what my wife said.
例えば、医者の健康概念は妻が言っていたことです。
A doctor may see patients for a lifetime
医師は生涯にわたって患者を診ることがある
Say he has a few thousand
彼は数千持っていると言う
that number is still very small
その数はまだ非常に少ないです
He has some conclusions, you need to be healthy
彼はいくつかの結論を出しました、あなたは健康でなければなりません
It's the fact that we do a lot of these health studies
実際、私たちはこうした健康に関する研究をたくさん行っています
Tens of thousands of people have been following them for an unknown number of years before reaching a conclusion
何万人もの人々が、結論に達するまで、未知数の年にわたって彼らを追跡してきた
But most of us rely on his impression
しかし、私たちのほとんどは彼の印象に依存しています
so you become more stubborn
だからあなたはもっと頑固になる
Georgian Airlines
ジョージアン航空
this is for us
これは私たちのためです
The academicians of Academia Sinica specially remind
中央研究院の学者らは特別に注意を促す。
Our academicians often go to various institutes to ask questions
私たちの学者は、質問するためにさまざまな機関によく行きます。
The question said everyone went up to report, right?
質問では、全員が報告に行ったということですよね？
Some fields are not related to him.
彼とは関係のない分野もあります。
But he has a lot of insights
しかし、彼は多くの洞察力を持っています
We can't say that what you said is wrong, what?
あなたが言ったことは間違っているとは言えませんが、何ですか？
can't say that
それは言えません
So it's very polite
だからとても丁寧なんです
so
それで
this is why
これが理由です
a sharp blade
鋭い刃
everyone has to be quite humble
誰もがかなり謙虚でなければなりません
just go to a field
ただ畑に行くだけ
you are not very familiar
あなたはあまり馴染みがありません
right
右
Actually I'm talking about AS
実はASのことを言ってるんです
I'm also worried
私も心配です
That is to say, I may say something that is
つまり、次のようなことが言えるかもしれません。
It's totally different from what people say
世間で言われていることと全く違います
So don't believe me all
だからみんな信じないでね
this
これ
This is to draw a Picture
これは絵を描くことです
above this is a
この上には
a young woman
若い女性
eyes here nose here
目はここに鼻はここに
then wear one
それから着てください
hat right?
帽子ですよね？
Did you guys see another image
別の画像を見ましたか
This is often psychologically
これは心理的に起こることがよくあります
some examples
いくつかの例
this is an old woman
これは老婦人です
this is her jaw
これは彼女の顎です
the same one
同じものです
If you take the lead and think so, you won't see the other picture
率先してそう思えば他の絵は見えなくなる
We often do this, this is the understanding of an article paragraph
私たちはよくこれを行いますが、これは記事の段落の理解です
This is borrowed from the same article from the teacher Chen Yixin of National Taiwan University.
これは、国立台湾大学のチェン・イーシン教師の同じ記事から借用したものです。
There are some conditions for the understanding of the sentence just mentioned
先ほど述べた文を理解するにはいくつかの条件があります
This article paragraph is more complex
この記事の段落はより複雑です
So you guys have to admire yourselves very much
だからあなたは自分自身を大いに賞賛しなければなりません
When this sentence is finished, you fully understand
この文が終わったら、完全に理解できます
it's really not easy
それは本当に簡単ではありません
Why? It's unlikely that a computer will do it
なぜでしょうか? コンピューターがそれを行う可能性は低いです
Although the new regulations and documents formulated by ordinary new districts are somewhat crude
一般の新区が策定する新条例や文書は少々荒削りではあるものの、
Some are only provisional
一部は暫定的なものです
have a halfway night in practice
練習で中途半端に過ごす
But this kind of legal system is only related to the practice of economic and social activities
しかし、この種の法制度は、経済的および社会的活動の実践にのみ関連しています。
Well received by domestic investors
国内投資家から好評
They think that investing in ordinary new districts is not easy for Changhua.
彼らは、彰化市にとって通常の新しい地区への投資は簡単ではないと考えている。
Rules and interests can be guaranteed
ルールと利益を保証できる
OK, if we want to analyze this
OK、これを分析したい場合は、
This is a formal analysis
これは正式な分析です
I split the previous words into paragraphs.
前の単語を段落に分割しました。
Each punctuation does not count as a paragraph, does it?
句読点はそれぞれ段落としてカウントされませんね。
This is despite the common area
共用エリアにも関わらずです
Some of the latter are supplementary, so they are called parallel
後者の一部は補足的なものであるため、並列と呼ばれます。
To be gradually improved, this is a juxtaposition, but a juxtaposition of upper and lower positions, not a parallel
徐々に改善していきますが、これは並置ですが、上下の位置の並置であり、平行ではありません
The same is true here, this rule of law is an explanatory way, and then there are several juxtaposed with the following
ここでも同じことが当てはまります。この法則は説明方法であり、次のような法則がいくつか並べてあります。
Then explain it to him, the last is the turning point, the turning point means that in the end he thinks, at the beginning although he said that even though
それから彼に説明してください、最後がターニングポイントです、ターニングポイントは、最初はそう言っていたのに、最終的には彼が考えることを意味します
Although there are a lot of shortcomings, but in the end I think there is still a way
欠点はたくさんありますが、最終的にはまだ方法があると思います
So when we look at it, we can understand it after reading it for a few seconds
だから、それを見ると、数秒読んだだけで理解できます
So why can't the computer do it now, ideally he can do it
では、なぜ今コンピューターはそれができないのでしょう、理想的にはそれができるのです
Such an exaggerated understanding is very difficult for a computer
このような大げさな理解はコンピュータにとって非常に困難です
So everyone knows that when it comes to natural language understanding, our human ability is now far beyond that of computers
したがって、自然言語理解に関しては、人間の能力がコンピューターの能力をはるかに超えていることは誰もが知っています。
but there are many reasons
でも理由はたくさんある
In the end, let's talk about what is called technique and what is called a good student at the beginning.
最後に、最初に技術と呼ばれるものと優等生と呼ばれるものについて話しましょう。
how to define
定義方法
This is my definition, just listen to it
これが私の定義です、聞いてください
That is, for each language concept, we assume that there is a corresponding question bank
つまり、言語概念ごとに、対応する質問バンクがあると仮定します。
That is to say, you think of it as saying that I am going to test a child today
つまり、今日は子供をテストすると言っているのと同じだと思います
Or a high school student, what questions are used to test him
それとも高校生、彼を試すためにどんな質問が使われるのか
Then this computer passed the same test
その後、このコンピュータは同じテストに合格しました
If the robot answers through this question bank
ロボットがこの質問バンクを通じて回答した場合
The question bank must be sampled, some each time
質問バンクは毎回サンプリングする必要があります
Reaching 70% counts for a few
70% に達するのは少数の場合です
So let's say he understands the concept, not that he's 100%
つまり、彼が 100% 理解しているわけではなく、概念を理解しているとしましょう。
In fact, we are here, and it is the same when I take the value license test in the United States.
実際、私たちはここにいますが、米国でバリューライセンス試験を受けるときも同様です。
American Exam Value is next to an examiner's seat
アメリカの試験値は試験官席の隣にあります
Then you pass and pass, right?
それで、どんどんパスしていきますよね？
He was glad that he was in a good mood that day, and many people had
彼はその日ご機嫌が良かったこと、そして多くの人が機嫌が良かったことをうれしく思いました。
Otherwise, many people
そうでなければ多くの人が
when i go to the exam
試験に行くとき
I visited Stanford in 1996
私は1996年にスタンフォードを訪れました
At that time, I had been driving in Taiwan for a long time
当時、私は台湾で長い間運転していました
Everyone knows the level of technology in Taiwan
台湾の技術レベルは誰もが知っています
There must be no problem driving in the US, right?
アメリカでの運転には問題ないはずですよね？
But I passed the exam three times
でも試験には3回合格した
Because he asked me about you as soon as he got in the car
車に乗るとすぐに彼はあなたのことを私に尋ねたので
Do you know how to drive it? I said it has been open for 20 years
運転してくれますか? 20 年前から営業していると言いました
This sentence alone has already deducted a lot of points from him.
この一文だけですでに彼からかなりの減点を受けている。
So in fact, he also has his own problems.
ですから実際には、彼自身の問題も抱えています。
he picks a few questions
彼はいくつかの質問を選んだ
For example, you make me a Pair of parking
たとえば、あなたは私をペアパーキングにしてくれます
leather parking or something
革製の駐車場か何か
Back into the garage, these things
ガレージに戻って、これらのもの
it's over if you know
知ってしまったら終わりです
It's basically not that difficult to understand here
基本的にここを理解するのはそれほど難しくありません
We are in a general company
私たちは普通の会社にいます
or we in society
あるいは社会にいる私たち
Many things have exam certification
試験認定のあるものも多い
So as long as we can handle a concept
コンセプトを扱える限り
relevant knowledge to be able to understand the concept
概念を理解するための関連知識
In fact, the cram school is doing this.
実際、学習塾はこれを行っています。
Now everyone knows that it is said to take a doctoral program and a master's program
博士課程と修士課程を取ると言われているのは今では誰もが知っています。
There are tutoring Ken
家庭教師のケンがいる
And they say there are about three
そして彼らは3つほどあると言います
Half of the students are admitted to Ph.D. through cram school
半数の学生が予備校経由で博士課程に進学
why? because the teacher is lazy
どうして？先生が怠け者だから
It's his archeology question.
それは彼の考古学に関する質問です。
They also changed
彼らも変わりました
His question bank is small
彼の質問バンクは少ないです
He also knows, so their students can recite it a little
彼も知っているので、生徒たちはそれを少し暗唱できます
So let's take care of a concept-related knowledge
では、概念関連の知識を大事にしましょう
sometimes it's not that hard
時にはそれはそれほど難しくありません
Let's talk about natural language understanding now
今度は自然言語理解について話しましょう
I just said that it takes a lot of knowledge
かなりの知識が必要だと言いました
How to acquire this knowledge
この知識を取得する方法
this is the most important point
これが最も重要な点です
The foundation of natural language understanding is knowledge
自然言語理解の基礎は知識です
Language is the most important power to record knowledge
言語は知識を記録する最も重要な力です
So learn from the language
だから言語から学びましょう
Language knowledge is divided into two parts
言語知識は 2 つの部分に分かれています
one is the rule
1つはルールです
For example, a rule of word formation
たとえば、単語の形成規則
What are the sentence patterns? Chinese Grammar
文型とは何ですか? 中国語の文法
belongs to this
これに属します
The advantage of this rule is that
このルールの利点は、
Our Chinese is subject verb object
私たちの中国語は主語動詞目的語です
This structure is most frequently
この構造は最も頻繁に見られます
so you swap anything
だからあなたは何でも交換します
become something else
別のものになる
Using this rule may be a legitimate argument
このルールの使用は正当な議論になる可能性があります
Although not necessarily meaningful
必ずしも意味があるわけではありませんが、
That's a lot of imagery experience
それはたくさんのイメージ体験です
For example, the sentence is fluent
たとえば、文章が流暢である
When you read it, you think this is very logical, right?
これを読むと、非常に論理的だと思いますよね?
Chinese medicine, this is even more difficult
漢方、これはさらに難しい
This is more statistical
これはより統計的です
So what we just said
それで、私たちが今言ったこと
remember many patterns
たくさんのパターンを覚えておく
Why learn a native speaker
なぜネイティブスピーカーを学ぶのか
He's not good at grammar
彼は文法が苦手です
Let's take the old beauty exam
昔の美人試験を受けてみよう
He can't pass you in English grammar
彼は英文法であなたを追い越せない
Because we learn English from grammar
私たちは英語を文法から学ぶので、
They learned from this ordinary chat
彼らはこの普通の雑談から学びました
So he is the impression
それで彼はその印象です
he still knows grammar
彼はまだ文法を知っています
But he doesn't have such a strong sense
でも彼はそこまで強い意識を持っていない
So he is fluent in this aspect
だから彼はこの点に関しては流暢だ
he is much stronger than you
彼はあなたよりもずっと強いです
the english book he read
彼が読んだ英語の本
there may be hundreds of copies
何百部もあるかもしれない
they have counted
彼らは数えた
i.e. a child
つまり子供
American children from childhood to college
幼少期から大学生までのアメリカの子供たち
He learns about ten words a day
彼は1日に約10単語を学びます
because when he went to college
なぜなら彼が大学に行ったとき
Learned more than 300,000 words
300,000語以上を学習
don't remember
覚えていない
But he really learned so many words
でも彼は本当にたくさんの言葉を学びました
So our memory is terrible
だから私たちの記憶力はひどいものだ
The following question is to say
次の質問はつまり、
Well, now the machine is also starting from scratch
さて、マシンもまたゼロからスタートです
How does he learn from so many materials?
彼はこれほど多くの資料からどうやって学ぶのでしょうか?
then you can learn
そうすれば学ぶことができます
what kind of degree
どのような学位ですか
We say that the most abundant textual information on the Internet
インターネット上で最も豊富なテキスト情報は、
Boundless language, semantic knowledge is indistinguishable from the text
無限の言語、意味知識はテキストと区別がつかない
This is for people to see
これは人に見てもらうためのものです
So in human terms you probably
人間の言葉で言えば、おそらくあなたは
We are now reading slowly because of reading
読書のせいで今はゆっくり読んでいます
Otherwise we can gain a lot of knowledge
そうでなければ、私たちは多くの知識を得ることができます
Then as far as the machine is concerned these are symbols
機械に関する限り、これらはシンボルです
Like the word Chen Shi
陳詩という言​​葉のように
and cuteness are two symbols
と可愛らしさの2つの象徴
where is the meaning
意味はどこにありますか
this is very difficult
これはとても難しいです
If you find that it uses ham try
ハムを使っていることがわかったら試してみてください
These are very challenging questions
これらは非常に難しい質問です
Google everyone knows
誰もが知っているグーグル
The recent Google translation is much better than before
最近のGoogle翻訳は以前に比べて格段に良くなりました
Just thanks to Deep Learning
まさにディープラーニングのおかげです
is the new machine learning of deep learning
ディープラーニングという新しい機械学習です
But the principle of its translation is
しかし、その翻訳の原則は、
Rely on many bilingual parallel intonations
多くのバイリンガルの並列イントネーションに依存
For example, we now have many
たとえば、今ではたくさんの
Chinese to English
中国語から英語へ
Or translate English into Chinese
または英語を中国語に翻訳してください
We have a lot of semantic information
意味論的な情報がたくさんあります
Already included in this translation
この翻訳にはすでに含まれています
so it goes to see
それで見に行きます
memorize this translation
この訳を覚えておいてください
Didn't I just talk about the phonetic conversion?
さっき発音変換の話をしたじゃないですか。
You go to memorize that Windows
Windows を覚えておきましょう
If you finish memorizing the seven characters in rhyme
七文字を韻で覚え終わったら
your ability is very strong
あなたの能力はとても強いです
a little harder to translate
翻訳するのが少し難しい
because it has an order that changes
順番が変わるから
So most if the order remains the same
したがって、順序が同じままであれば、ほとんどの場合
It actually flips pretty well
実際はかなり良く回転します
That first Google translation
初めてのGoogle翻訳
actually simpler
実際にはもっと単純です
Not using Deep Learning
ディープラーニングを使用しない
It is an Algorithm written by one person
一人で書いたアルゴリズムです
Because at that time the key point of the translation was to say
なぜなら、当時の翻訳の重要なポイントは次のようなものだったからです。
It has about 30 languages ​​in the world
世界には約30の言語があります
There are always people who need to turn over and over again.
何度も何度もひっくり返さなければならない人が常にいます。
Of course, the translation to English is the most frequent
もちろん、英語への翻訳が最も頻繁に行われます。
Then these 30 languages
それでは、これらの 30 の言語
Both have information about the counterpart in English
両方とも英語でお互いについての情報を持っています
So there's a lot of these data out there
こういったデータは世の中にたくさんあります
So this guy wrote an Algorithm
それでこの人はアルゴリズムを書きました
How to use statistical methods for translation
翻訳に統計的手法を使用する方法
don't understand at all
まったくわかりません
Just use statistics to find out
統計を使用して調べてください
After the translation, there are 35 languages
翻訳後の言語は 35 言語になります
translated into 35 languages
35か国語に翻訳
all can each other
全員がお互いにできる
very fast
とても早い
whether it is good or not is another matter
それが良いかどうかは別問題
It's doing better now
今は良くなってきています
So learning the language of these online
オンラインでこれらの言語を学ぶ
There are two ways
2つの方法があります
One is Rule Base
1 つはルールベースです
In the early stage, before 1990, the Rule Base model was the main model.
1990 年以前の初期段階では、ルール ベース モデルが主要なモデルでした。
different knowledge
異なる知識
First divide it into clusters and categories
まずクラスタとカテゴリに分割します
Then write the relevant rules for each class
次に、各クラスに関連するルールを記述します。
The same class is more like and easier to write
同じクラスのほうが似ていて書きやすい
The advantage is that its true or false examples are relatively easy to figure out why
利点は、その真偽の例が理由を理解するのが比較的簡単であることです。
As we did knowledge law the earliest
知識法を最も早く行ったように
At that time also Rule Base
当時もルールベース
So when it's wrong you can know right away why
そのため、間違っている場合は、その理由をすぐに知ることができます
The system is more stable
システムがより安定しました
easy to handle this particular case
この特定のケースに対処するのは簡単です
Then suitable for inference operations
推論操作に適しています
Almost all large-scale systems in the industry are Rule Base
業界の大規模システムのほとんどはルールベースです
because you are in industry
あなたは業界にいるから
you make a system
あなたがシステムを作るのです
you tell the boss this
あなたは上司にこれを言います
this is wrong
これは間違っています
If you know your mistakes, you can make amends
自分の間違いを知っていれば、償うことができる
It will be corrected tomorrow
明日修正される予定です
Rule BaseDo it
ルールベースやってみよう
if you do it in another way
別の方法でやれば
The disadvantage is that the rules are written by humans, which is very labor-intensive
欠点は、ルールが人間によって作成されるため、非常に労力がかかることです。
The subjective consciousness of different people is very different, and the rules of writing will conflict
人によって主観的な意識は大きく異なり、文章のルールが衝突する場合があります。
And people can cover a limited range
そして人がカバーできる範囲は限られています
All of us have a teacher Su Keyi, he does machine translation
私たち全員には Su Keyi という先生がいます。彼は機械翻訳をしてくれます。
He is really doing it, he used to run a company outside
彼は本当にやってるよ、以前は外で会社を経営していたんだ
His machine translation first used Rubber Bass
彼の機械翻訳は最初にラバーベースを使用しました
Encountered a problem, the first
最初の問題が発生しました
He hired quite a few linguists and often quarreled
彼はかなりの数の言語学者を雇い、よく喧嘩した
He said I made him right, and you made him bad, you write one, you talk about me
彼は、私が彼を正しくし、あなたが彼を悪くした、あなたが何かを書いて、あなたが私のことを話すと言いました
What about this?
これはどうですか？
He later said that he fires a linguist every time
彼は後に、毎回言語学者を解雇していると語った。
He improves accuracy
彼は精度を向上させます
He said that it is best for a company to be written by one person, and there will be no quarrel
彼は、会社は一人で書いたほうがいい、そうすれば争いも起こらない、と言いました。
Well, there are some companies now
今、いくつかの会社があります
His general manager is his earliest Founder is a weak person
彼のゼネラルマネージャーは彼の最初の創業者である 創設者は弱い人間である
He said I would never be FIRE
彼は私がFIREになることは決してないだろうと言いました
Because if he leaves, his company will collapse
彼が辞めたら会社が潰れるから
conflicts between rules
ルール間の衝突
Like Microsoft they are doing Cortena
Microsoftのように、彼らはCortenaを開発中です
The same goes for voice assistants
音声アシスタントも同様です
he can answer questions
彼は質問に答えることができます
He's doing about 12 fields now
彼は現在約12の畑をやっています
Traveling, what about ordering food?
旅行中、食べ物の注文はどうですか?
or this
またはこれ
Meteorology, and constellations
気象学と星座
But every time he wants to add a new field, it will be troublesome
でも、新しいフィールドを追加するたびに面倒になる
Because of this new field added problems
この新しいフィールドにより問題が追加されました
knowledge
知識
will conflict with the previous
前のものと競合します
So he will steal other people's problems
だから彼は他人の問題を盗むだろう
It's very troublesome to grab and grab
掴んだり掴んだりするのがとても面倒
So this is if being the biggest problem
これが最大の問題であるとすれば
then let me give an example
それでは例を挙げてみましょう
This is difficult to standardize in English literature
これを英語文学で標準化するのは困難です
That is to say, you are behind the English paper
つまり、あなたは英語の新聞の背後にいます
There are references
参考文献があります
Inside the author and title journal, one is drawn out
著者名とタイトル日記の中に、1つが描かれています
This is followed by Volume issue, Pace number
これにボリュームの問題、ペース数が続きます
To extract one, you have to write a lot of rules
1 つを抽出するには、多くのルールを記述する必要があります
sorry, drink some water
ごめんなさい、水を飲んでください
it's exactly an hour
ちょうど1時間です
Then the first Rule means that the Volume needs to be shaved, and Esho will shave again.
次に、最初のルールは、ボリュームをシェービングする必要があることを意味し、Esho は再度シェービングします。
All good, write one every time you encounter a different situation
大丈夫です。別の状況に遭遇するたびに書いてください
OK, this is the basic Rule. After Volume, you need to vaccinate and shave, then come to Esho, and then come to something
OK、これが基本的なルールです。ボリュームの後は、ワクチン接種と髭剃りを行ってからエショーに来て、その後何かをする必要があります
it is written as a rule
ルールとして書いてある
The parameter is also different for active learning, it uses the plot rate or the gold-like network to learn
アクティブラーニングではパラメーターも異なり、プロットレートまたはゴールドライクネットワークを使用して学習します
The current mainstream language processing technology is these two
現在主流の言語処理技術はこの2つ
It mainly replaces this problem with a mathematical optimization problem
主にこの問題を数学的最適化問題に置き換えます。
Optimization is having an objective with a number of
最適化とは、いくつかの目標を持つことです。
Then you input this one input later
次に、これを後で入力します
it is right and wrong it can learn
それは正しいことも間違っていることも学ぶことができる
Statistical models need to do a lot of feature engineering
統計モデルでは多くの特徴エンジニアリングを行う必要があります
But for deep learning it is less necessary
しかし、ディープラーニングは比較的不要です
But it needs a lot of data to train
ただし、トレーニングするには大量のデータが必要です
In fact, most deep learning
実際、ディープラーニングのほとんどは、
probably in the company
おそらく会社内で
Only big companies can do well
大企業だけがうまくやっていける
This is known as a high degree of automation
これは高度な自動化として知られています
In fact, the preparation of the previous materials is very labor-intensive.
実際、事前の資料の準備は非常に手間がかかります。
It didn't mention this
これについては言及されていませんでした
The disadvantage is that these three shortcomings are probably difficult for ordinary companies to accept
欠点は、これら 3 つの欠点がおそらく一般の企業には受け入れられにくいことです。
results are unpredictable
結果は予測不可能です
Let's say you added some new training knowledge
新しいトレーニングの知識を追加したとします。
it might be wrong with some old ones
古いものだと間違っているかもしれません
it has no way of explaining why it's good
なぜそれが良いのかを説明する方法はありません
If we know our mistakes, we can correct them
自分の間違いを知っていれば、それを修正することができます
it is hard to change
変えるのは難しい
Why do many big companies not change
なぜ多くの大企業は変わらないのか
he is willing to use
彼は喜んで使います
So he usually treats those with higher frequency
したがって、彼の出現頻度は通常より高いです
relatively high accuracy
比較的高い精度
otherwise lower
それ以外の場合は低い
So there are some special cases that he can't handle at all.
したがって、彼がまったく処理できない特殊なケースがいくつかあります。
long distance relationship
遠距離恋愛
Those are relatively low frequency
それらは比較的低い頻度です
is also difficult to deal with
対処するのも難しい
the hardest thing is to say
最も難しいことは言うことです
He has a bottleneck in accuracy
彼には精度の点でボトルネックがある
He can't make it up to more than one level
彼は複数のレベルに上がることができない
Because you have a lot of very detailed knowledge, he can't use it
彼はあなたの詳しい知識を使えないから
So we draw a very simple graph
そこで非常に単純なグラフを描きます
Parametric machine learning is a black box job
パラメトリック機械学習はブラックボックスの仕事です
So he has a window to see the kitchen
彼のキッチンには窓があるので見えません
Then the back of the entrance is where you can see what he does.
そして、入り口の裏側は、彼が何をしているのかを見ることができる場所です。
be more at ease
もっと安心してください
Glassbox
ガラスボックス
Let's show you now
今すぐ見せてみましょう
Some examples of deep learning used in machine translation
機械翻訳で使用されるディープラーニングの例
Even he doesn't talk about understanding
彼でさえ理解については話さない
He just made the translation as good as he thought it would be
彼はただ自分が思った通りに良い翻訳をしただけだ
But this so-called best has a frequency standard
しかし、このいわゆるベストには周波数の基準があります
not for ordinary people
普通の人のためではない
This is a translator to understand personnel
人材を理解するための翻訳者です
what do you think, with considerable difficulty
どう思いますか、かなり難しいです
This English is better, you can see
この英語のほうが上手です、わかりますか
這個不 make sense to understand how people want to have considerable difficulty
這個不、人々がどのようにかなりの困難を望んでいるのかを理解するのは理にかなっています
just don't write anything, right?
ただ何も書かないだけですよね？
That's a better way
それはより良い方法です
to understand how people think is very difficult
人々がどのように考えているかを理解することは非常に難しい
Then below is I ask my secretary to take down the telephone number
次に、秘書に電話番号をメモするように依頼します。
I asked my secretary and took down the phone number
私は秘書に尋ねて電話番号を書き留めた
This is a mistake, not to ask the secretary
これは間違いです、秘書に頼まなかったのです
Good translation is I ask the secretary to take down this phone number
良い翻訳は、秘書にこの電話番号をメモするようお願いします
So his, in fact, turned over with a plan and a concession
それで、実際、彼は計画と譲歩を持ってひっくり返したのです
Most of this is true, but because he doesn't understand
これのほとんどは真実ですが、彼は理解していないため、
So those words together don't make sense
だから、これらの言葉を合わせても意味がありません
再來說 I ask my secretary to take down the letter
再來說 秘書に手紙を書き留めるように頼みます
This is to test him on purpose, he will definitely not
これは彼を意図的にテストするためです、彼は絶対にそうではありません
i asked my secretary to take the letter
私は秘書に手紙を受け取るように頼んだ
In fact, he means in Chinese that I dictate this letter and ask the secretary to write it down
実際、彼は中国語で、私がこの手紙を口述筆記し、秘書に書き留めるよう頼むと言っています。
This is the correct English meaning
これが正しい英語の意味です
下面是Big Trucks are forbidden in this road to make room for small cars
以下は小型車のためのスペースを確保するため、この道路では大型トラックの通行が禁止されています
Big trucks banned on this road to make room for smaller cars
小型車用のスペースを確保するため、この道路では大型トラックの通行が禁止されています
Is there any reference value for him?
彼にとっての基準値はありますか？
Probably not even reference value
おそらく参考値にもならない
Generally speaking, there is a reference value, and if I miss a word or two, I will correct it, right?
大体、基準値があって、一語二語聞き逃したら修正しますよね。
If he has to rewrite this, he doesn't need to rewrite it at all.
これを書き直す必要がある場合でも、まったく書き直す必要はありません。
A better translation is that big trucks are not allowed on this road and small cars are allowed to pass
より適切な翻訳は、この道路は大型トラックの通行が許可されておらず、小型車の通行が許可されているということです。
This is more like people
こっちの方が人間らしいよ
If you understand this sentence, it's okay if you don't speak fluently.
この文が理解できれば、流暢に話せなくても大丈夫です。
But sometimes you mean the wrong thing
でも時々あなたは間違ったことを言っている
If you don't understand English today and you need to translate it, it will be very troublesome
今日英語が分からなくて翻訳する必要がある場合、とても面倒です
So we use the following example to talk about unified self-selection
そこで、次の例を使用して、統合された自己選択について説明します。
Taipei is a child smuggled
台北は密輸された子供だ
I’ve read it today, don’t read the following, you’ll probably understand it right away
今日読みました。以下は読まないでください。おそらくすぐに理解できると思います
But in fact there are many words below
しかし、実際には以下の単語がたくさんあります
I'm omitting the part of the word now, just the word
今は単語の一部を省略して、単語だけを書きます
Taipei City Taipei City one by one
台北市 台北市 ひとつずつ
There are many possibilities, right?
可能性はたくさんありますよね？
But there is only one meaningful combination
しかし、意味のある組み合わせは 1 つだけです
And what you are hearing is the 11 children in Taipei
そしてあなたが聞いているのは台北の11人の子供たちです
the part that is red
赤い部分
I didn't hear anything else
他には何も聞こえませんでした
Actually not heard
実際には聞いていない
You are the same master as Xia Qi
あなたは Xia Qi と同じマスターです
You are 99% enumerated by you
あなたは99%あなたによって列挙されています
You quickly find out that doesn't work
それがうまくいかないことはすぐにわかります
So his homophonic choice
つまり彼の同音異義語の選択は
That is, each one is an input sound
つまり、それぞれが入力音です
Then there are single-character and two-character words below
次に、1 文字と 2 文字の単語が下にあります。
he doesn't know which one you want to choose
彼はあなたがどれを選びたいのか知りません
So you use a mathematical model to calculate
したがって、数学的モデルを使用して計算します
In the end you may choose the yellow one
最終的には黄色を選ぶかも知れません
not necessarily right
必ずしも正しくない
Then it depends on whether your mathematical model is well written.
次に、数学モデルが適切に記述されているかどうかに依存します。
Now let's see where the difficulty of this problem lies.
では、この問題の難しさはどこにあるのか見てみましょう。
the pattern recognition
パターン認識
On the choice of homophonic system
同音異義語システムの選択について
I hit one
1つ当たりました
The phonetic book in Taiwan also needs to be toned
台湾のふりがな帳もトーンアップする必要がある
right
右
Then I just talked about five to fifteen unisons
それから私はちょうど5〜15のユニゾンについて話しました
The mainland is silent
本土は沈黙している
the one it triples
3倍になるもの
Three times as many words is fifteen to forty-five word possibilities
3 倍の単語は 15 ～ 45 単語の可能性があります
so this is the doctor
それでこれが医者です
All Physicians Gotta Get It All Right
すべての医師はすべてを正しく理解する必要があります
very many homophones and words
同音異義語や単語が非常に多い
It is not necessarily a statement, some are homonyms
必ずしもステートメントではありません、一部は同音異義語です
There are still a lot of grabbing words, and the grabbing words are next to it
掴み言葉はまだたくさんある、掴み言葉はその隣にある
Like this is the lion, sent to the hospital, the market, what kind of toothpaste
これはライオンです、病院に送られます、市場に送られます、どんな歯磨き粉ですか
So when you beat the doctor down
それで医者を打ち負かしたとき
You have to do it right, not him right, everything next to him has to be right
彼が正しくではなく、あなたが正しくやらなければならない、彼の隣にあるものはすべて正しくなければならない
a whole bunch of restrictions like this
このような制限がたくさんあります
So we just said that the seven-character Window can be memorized like this
つまり、7 文字の Window は次のように記憶できると言いました。
It's possible to solve this problem
この問題を解決することは可能です
It's a pity that we humans are not very creative in speech
残念なことに、私たち人間はスピーチにおいてあまり創造的ではありません
Everything we say is written into a certain paragraph of text.
私たちが話すことはすべて、テキストの特定の段落に書き込まれます。
Let me give you an example to show you the homonym context
同音異義語の文脈を示す例を示しましょう
We used to do smart calligraphy as well
スマートカリグラフィーもやってました
dermatology, so we'll write
皮膚科なので書きます
If the front is dermatology, internal medicine, cancer
フロントが皮膚科・内科・がんなら
The latter subject is river fighting, right?
後者の主題は川の戦いですよね？
Then the doctor's words are Muge Branch
そこで医師の言葉は ムゲ支店
if there is an after
アフターがあるなら
bump into dermatology
皮膚科にぶつかる
If you are a nuclear medicine doctor, the two should be discussed together
あなたが核医学の医師であれば、この 2 つを一緒に議論する必要があります。
This nuclear cool medical score is a little higher than his
この核クール医療スコアは彼のものより少し高いです
But if I say the following, you will be miserable
でも次のようなことを言ったらあなたは不幸になるでしょう
To treat this kind of allergic skin, physicians only have experience
この種のアレルギー性皮膚の治療には、経験豊富な医師のみが必要です
This is the saying, if you don’t know how to do it, you will do it wrong
これは格言です、やり方を知らなければ間違ったことをするでしょう
You just use points, one high and one low, you will definitely not be able to do it
高いところと低いところのポイントを使うだけでは絶対に無理です
Because there are tens of thousands of my way of speaking, it is impossible to do it right
私の話し方は何万通りもあるから、正しくやるのは不可能
So we now propose that what we just talked about is that
そこで、私たちが今話したことは次のようなことだと提案します。
What others have done, we now propose a way
他の人が行ってきたことを、私たちは次の方法で提案します
We believe it is a very simple one
それは非常に簡単なことだと私たちは信じています
And that's what I just said about using Pattern Recognition
これがパターン認識の使用について先ほど述べたことです
Pattern Recognition, we think that language learning is basically Pattern Matching
パターン認識、私たちは言語学習は基本的にパターンマッチングであると考えています
When people see the difference between machines, they will generate it when they learn
人間は機械の違いを認識すると、学習時にそれを生み出します。
More abstract Patterns will be remembered
より抽象的なパターンが記憶される
In this way, if I learn one sentence, I may be able to watch many dramas and understand many sentences
こうやって一つの文を覚えれば、たくさんのドラマを見て、たくさんの文を理解できるようになるかもしれません
Like this below, Hon Hai Foxconn Technology Group
以下のように、Hon Hai Foxconn Technology Group
Shenzhen division of labor, this is just an organization name
深セン分業、これは単なる組織名です
will produce smart machines
スマートマシンを生み出すだろう
If I knew it was an institution when I read it
読んだときにそれが機関だとわかっていたら
This sentence is very simple, isn't it?
この文はとても簡単ですね。
This is followed by the name of a gene
これに遺伝子の名前が続きます
incase tumor necrosis factor receptor
腫瘍壊死因子受容体の場合
partner factor
パートナー要因
The words of this man who doesn't understand life
人生を知らない男の言葉
Absolutely impossible to know that this is a gene
これが遺伝子であることを知ることは絶対に不可能です
Now it's time to teach the computer to read all this
さあ、コンピューターにこれらすべてを読み取るように教える時が来ました。
How much knowledge is needed
どれくらいの知識が必要なのか
The following is the relationship extraction
関係抽出は以下の通り
Like MIRNA induced atopsis targeting BCl2
BCl2を標的とするMIRNA誘発性アトプシスと同様
Only biological people can't read this
生物学者だけがこれを読むことができません
Now we ask the computer to say
ここで、コンピュータにこう言わせます。
it needs to be able
それができる必要がある
It used to be said that a computer should be able to operate in a very harsh environment
かつては、コンピュータは非常に過酷な環境でも動作できる必要があると言われていました。
nothing to be afraid of going swimming
泳ぎに行くのは何も恐れることはありません
Now that's bad too
もうそれもダメだよ
It's just that most of the creatures can't read.
ただ、ほとんどの生き物は文字が読めません。
to be able to read him
彼の言葉を読めるようになるために
Then extract the relation
次に関係を抽出します
question category
問題分類
like does anyone know
誰か知っていますか？
This fragrant tree duck restaurant in Tainan
台南の香り豊かな木鴨レストラン
This is our test robot
これが私たちのテストロボットです
will you understand
理解できますか
What are the must-eat foods in Taipei?
台北で必ず食べるべき食べ物は何ですか?
near MRT station
MRT駅近く
will you understand
理解できますか
I can't understand now
今は理解できません
There are many other patterns
他にも色々なパターンがあります
let's see now
今見てみましょう
Our present model is
私たちの現在のモデルは
We used to have a dream
私たちにはかつて夢がありました
It is pattern matching
パターンマッチングです
if
もしも
The first rule is written by the machine itself
最初のルールはマシン自体によって記述されます
And it's flexible when it's right
適切な場合には柔軟に対応します
Is it possible to apply a rule we just talked about to be
先ほど話したルールを適用することは可能でしょうか？
One is the Impressionist Statistical
一つは印象派の統計です。
Both models kind of all fit together
両方のモデルはある意味ぴったり合っています
high automation
高度な自動化
Accuracy is highly interpretable
精度は非常に解釈可能です
easy to explain is important
説明しやすさが重要
Let us now look at the phenomenon of language
ここで言語現象を見てみましょう
what kind of
どんな
In fact, everyone knows
実は誰もが知っている
Is the spelling checker in English correct?
英語のスペルチェッカーは正しいですか?
It's because you mistyped an English word
それは英単語を打ち間違えたからです
he immediately
彼はすぐに
especially now on mobile
特に今はモバイルで
all playing
みんな遊んでる
Wrong two and he'll correct you, right?
2 つ間違えたら、彼が訂正してくれるでしょう?
So this Jinshi comparison actually existed very early.
つまり、この壬氏の比較は実際には非常に早い段階から存在していました。
is there a way to replace this
これを置き換える方法はありますか
It's just what I said, happy three, happy four, or some more boring words
それはただ私が言ったことだ、ハッピースリー、ハッピーフォー、あるいはもっと退屈な言葉
Now we humans will not be affected at all, we can all understand
これで、私たち人間はまったく影響を受けなくなります、私たちは皆理解できます
Like when we do voice input, there are many RRRs in the middle
音声入力のときみたいに途中にRRRがたくさんある
We can automatically tune these sounds of the drum position, as if we heard them or not
これらのドラムポジションの音を、聞こえているか聞こえないかのように自動的に調整できます。
What we do now is actually the same as printing me with this word
私たちが今していることは、実際には私にこの言葉を印刷するのと同じです
Automatically group these patterns with similarities and differences, and then find a representative
これらのパターンを類似点と相違点で自動的にグループ化し、代表的なパターンを見つけます。
Use these representatives to compare
これらの代表者を使用して比較してください
This we call the principle-based approach
これを原則ベースのアプローチと呼びます
Already applying for a patent
すでに特許出願中
Then this principle-based approach only needs to use a small number of principles
この原則ベースのアプローチでは、少数の原則のみを使用する必要があります。
This principle is a bit like RRR, but its advantage is that it is automatically written
この原則は RRR に少し似ていますが、その利点は自動的に書き込まれることです。
And its match comparison is very flexible
一致比較は非常に柔軟です
Let's use a few examples to see the power of using this principle-match
いくつかの例を使用して、この原則一致を使用することの威力を見てみましょう。
Like Chinese addresses, we used to write rules to ensure that
中国の住所と同様に、私たちは次のことを保証するためのルールを作成していました。
If I want to make a computer software now
今からパソコンソフトを作りたいと思ったら
Mark all the addresses written on the Internet
インターネット上に書かれたすべてのアドレスにマークを付けます
how much effort it takes
どれだけの努力が必要か
He skipped this one, sorry
彼はこれを飛ばしました、ごめんなさい
OK, I'll skip this paragraph first
OK、最初にこの段落をスキップします
It is the number of this pattern of the address
このアドレスのパターンの番号です
Generally, when you go out to write the mutual gathering address, this is probably how you write it.
一般的に相互集合の宛名を書きに行くときは、このように書くのではないでしょうか。
Shidaan District, Taipei, Shidaan District, Central East, right?
台北市師大安区、中東区師大安区ですよね？
not revealing
明らかにしない
But we know that addresses are often not
しかし、アドレスは多くの場合そうではないことを私たちは知っています。
no write zone
書き込みゾーンなし
So this time you may have another address like this
したがって、今回はこのような別のアドレスがある可能性があります
Sometimes you will add another Dongyang East Taxi No. 17 Shidaan in the center of Taipei
場合によっては、台北中心部の東陽東タクシー 17 番師大安を追加することもあります。
This plus these things is very harmful to the weak quilt
これとこれらのことは、弱いキルトにとって非常に有害です
Because it is written behind it, it must be connected to the road or connected to the area
後ろに書いてあるので、道路につながっているか、地域につながっているはずです。
then you are not at all
それならあなたは全くそうではありません
so you hook this thing up
それで、これを接続します
But speaking from someone who has tried it, this is not a problem at all
しかし、試してみた人の意見を言えば、これはまったく問題ありません
One point is that it is the same as the R2 we mentioned, it will turn green immediately
1 点は、先ほどの R2 と同じで、すぐに緑色になります。
So now when we make a computer, we must be able to put these things that should be placed or can be omitted.
ですから、今私たちがコンピューターを作るときには、こういう入れるべきもの、省略してもいいものを入れなければなりません。
all can be learned
すべてを学ぶことができます
Like ours, we know it by means of statistics
私たちと同じように、私たちは統計によってそれを知っています
So now the rules we wrote in the past probably need thirty or forty rules.
したがって、過去に作成したルールにはおそらく 30 ～ 40 のルールが必要になります。
Because I don't know if you start from Taipei or from Da'an District
台北からスタートするのか大安地区からスタートするのか分からないので
Then I don't know if you end up with number or None or something
その場合、最終的に数字になるのか、None になるのか、それとも何かになるのかはわかりません。
So write a bunch of rules
だからたくさんのルールを書いてください
Now only one Pattern is needed to calculate all the additions and subtractions
すべての加算と減算を計算するために必要なパターンは 1 つだけになりました。
Then this is the best speech recognition test
これが最良の音声認識テストです
You can't say Google Siri right now
今は Google Siri と言うことができません
That is to say, it mainly pairs the word with the noun that follows it.
つまり、主に単語とそれに続く名詞を組み合わせます。
Flowers should be matched with this wooden signature, and signatures should be matched with this word
花はこの木のサインと一致し、サインはこの言葉と一致する必要があります
So here I used to do natural calligraphy because I spent a lot of effort to get it right
ここでは、正しく書くために多大な努力を費やしたので、以前はナチュラルカリグラフィーを使用していました
It's very hard to write, I don't know how many bettors
書くのはとても難しい、ベッターが何人いるのかわからない
Then once this academician came to test
それから、この学者がテストに来たとき、
This academician is very smart, he added a posture after the posture
この学者はとても賢いです、彼は姿勢の後に姿勢を追加しました
Immediately the system is all wrong
すぐにシステムがすべて間違ってしまいます
Another academician made him cute and pottery
別の学者が彼を可愛く陶器にしました
A very pompous approach
とても尊大なアプローチ
So these systems are written cleanly
したがって、これらのシステムはきれいに書かれています
It is connected to this behind the bathing pool, connected to this
温水プールの後ろでこれにつながっています、これにつながっています
can't just add
単に追加することはできません
Delation I don’t want all the cute ones
Delation 可愛いものばかりはいらない
Don't do anything, see if you're right
何もしないで、自分が正しいかどうか確認してください
Now we basically know all of these
これで基本的にこれらすべてがわかりました
We now only need to write a Pattern
あとはパターンを書くだけです
Digit Quantity Agit
桁数行為
Because we already know that these other added Janes
なぜなら、これらの他の追加されたジェーンがすでに知っているからです
It's the same as those addresses just now
さっきのアドレスと同じです
Your noun bath pool you can write two or three
名詞のバスプールを 2 つまたは 3 つ書くことができます
Write something very cute on the front
表面にとてもかわいいものを書きます
whatever you write will be right
あなたが書いたことは何でも正しいでしょう
So it only has one Pattern and it will all be solved for you
したがって、パターンは 1 つだけで、すべて解決されます。
A lot of English literature we just talked about
先ほど話した多くの英語文学
It happens that writing a thousand rules is not enough
千のルールを書くだけでは十分ではない場合があります
Everyone knows English literature on the Internet
インターネット上の英語文学は誰もが知っています
it has the standard wording
標準的な文言が入っている
the same document
同じ文書
you can write it in many different ways
さまざまな方法で書くことができます
Can you guess how many spellings there are?
スペルが何種類あるか推測できますか?
i will give you a number now
今から番号を教えます
Raise your hand if you think the approximate number is correct
おおよその数字が正しいと思う場合は手を挙げてください
100 different spellings
100の異なるスペル
like this are different ways of writing
このように色々な書き方があります
What is the cap number and the bean number is written differently
キャップナンバーとビーンナンバーの表記が違うのは何ですか
Raise your hand if you guess 100
100だと思う人は手を挙げてください
1000's
1000年代
good 5000
良い5000
strangeness
奇妙さ
How many people think the rest
残りは何人だと思う？
10,000
10,000
OK thank you
わかりました、ありがとう
The answer is more than 8600
答えは8600以上です
Just such a simple document
こんなに簡単な書類なのに
More than 8600 kinds
8600種類以上
So if you're going to learn
それで、もし学ぶつもりなら
this will be dead
これは死ぬだろう
Our current approach is very simple, just write a lot of rules here, so a thousand is not enough, right?
私たちの現在のアプローチは非常にシンプルで、ここに多くのルールを記述するだけなので、1,000 では十分ではありません。
We are very simple now, we know what can be connected behind this volume 38,
私たちは今とてもシンプルです、この第 38 巻の背後に何が接続できるかを知っています。
You can pick up something on the left side of the issue and memorize it. This can be done with statistics, and there is no need for that person to take care of it.
問題の左側にあるものをピックアップして記憶することができますが、これは統計で行うことができ、その人が管理する必要はありません。
The same is true, issue and page number, what can be added in the middle, remember it with statistics,
同じように、号とページ番号、途中に何を追加できるか、統計で覚えてください、
Then we only have one pattern, which is VIP, volume issue, and page number, and include all of these,
その場合、パターンは 1 つだけです。VIP、巻号、ページ番号であり、これらすべてが含まれます。
This method is also the same, just like the address just now, because I am the same, a principle,
この方法も、先ほどの御答弁と同じで、私も同じですので、原則として、
Let's compare the error rate with the best active learning, CRF, because the accuracy is already very high,
精度がすでに非常に高いため、最高の能動学習である CRF と誤り率を比較してみましょう。
So in reverse, our error is 0.5, which is 99.5% right,
逆に、誤差は 0.5 で、99.5% 正しいことになります。
That's a little better, it's 98.8%, the page here is much better, what are these, standard learning,
それは少し良くなりました、98.8% です、ここのページはもっと良くなります、これは何ですか、標準学習、
Two thousand articles to test
2,000 件の記事をテストする
there are other testing agencies
他にも検査機関はあります
Our performance at each testing agency
各試験機関での実績
Performance is almost the same
性能はほぼ同じ
The last level is actually the hardest
最後のレベルは実際には最も難しいです
It's called FreeStar
フリースターといいます
FreeStar what
フリースターって何？
Many researchers from our Academia Sinica
中央研究院の多くの研究者
The book that was written after him wrote down
彼が書き留めた後に書かれた本
Because when our researchers wrote
なぜなら、私たちの研究者が書いたとき、
They all miss three and miss four, right?
みんな3つも4つも逃してるじゃないですか。
then that
それからそれ
He can understand you can understand
彼は理解できる、あなたも理解できる
But the computer can't understand
でもコンピュータには理解できない
So you go to use this more formal study
したがって、このより正式な研究を使用することになります
He is very wrong
彼はとても間違っています
Error force fast to 10
エラーは 10 まで強制的に高速化されます
OSA is approaching 10
OSAは10に近づいています
TITLE is 28.9
タイトルは28.9です
Journal and everything are messed up
日記も何もかもめちゃくちゃだ
After he has learned the standard
彼は標準を学んだ後、
Run these tests in general
一般的にこれらのテストを実行します
But our system basically handles very high
しかし、私たちのシステムは基本的に非常に高いものを処理します
It's almost as accurate as the original
オリジナルとほぼ同じ精度です
So this way
それで、こうして
Like what's in Taipei Social Home Center
台北ソーシャルホームセンターのようなもの
I don't care if you join me or not
あなたが私に加わるかどうかは気にしません
It's easy to learn a lot
多くのことを学ぶのは簡単です
then this can
それならこれでできます
Everyone, just say anything
みなさん、何でも言ってください
I can show you thirty or forty possibilities
30 か 40 の可能性をお見せできます
The distance between the two places is from Taipei to Kaohsiung
台北と高雄の間の距離
say 360 kilometers
360キロと言いますか
360 kilometers from Taipei to Kaohsiung
台北から高雄まで360キロ
do not write yes ah do not write what
はい、ああ、何を書かないでください
How many kilometers is the distance between Taipei and Kaohsiung?
台北と高雄の間の距離は何キロですか?
actually mean the same thing
実際には同じことを意味します
then if you are
もしあなたがそうなら
Go online and answer these questions
オンラインにアクセスしてこれらの質問に答えてください
it is written slightly differently
少し違って書かれています
You're going to write the rules, you can't finish
ルールを書こうとしていて、書き終えることはできない
So our final conclusion is that
したがって、私たちの最終的な結論は次のとおりです。
It's just P1
ただのP1だよ
The first location, the second location and the description of the distance
最初の場所、2 番目の場所と距離の説明
The distance between images and the distance value
画像間の距離と距離値
These few will never change
この少数は決して変わらない
It doesn't matter if it can be mapped or deleted
マッピングできるか削除できるかは関係ありません
The second way of writing is that you write the distance in the middle
2つ目の書き方は、真ん中に距離を書くことです。
Probably only these two patterns
たぶんこの2パターンだけ
describe all the relationships
すべての関係を説明する
For example, when we actually do it, put this Pattern
例えば実際にやるときはこのPatternを入れます
Can automatically Summarize out
自動で要約できる
It's not written by humans, it's written by computers
人間が書いたものではなく、コンピューターが書いたものです
Then it is very easy to compare
それなら比較するのはとても簡単です
So let's now look at the smart agent application
それでは、スマート エージェント アプリケーションを見てみましょう
12 minutes left
残り12分
Talk about some of the more important applications of this
これのより重要な応用例について話します
Smart Classification System
スマート分類システム
Now our mail
さて、私たちのメール
Emails you have received
受信したメール
Usually we do that in Zhongyuanyuan
通常は中原園で行います。
or on Google
またはGoogleで
will remove SpamMail first
まずSpamMailを削除します
Then SpamMail has many methods of Detect
SpamMail には多くの検出方法があります
But I usually pick up the phone or
でも、普段は電話に出たり、
I didn't read it for a while and wrote 100 new letters
しばらく読まなかったので、新たに100通の手紙を書きました
I can't accept it, right?
受け入れられないですよね？
What is the email system we want?
私たちが求める電子メール システムとは何ですか?
It can put this important and urgent Email at the top
この重要かつ緊急のメールを先頭に置くことができます
For example, there are five
たとえば、5つあります
For example, the vice president's office called you
たとえば、副大統領室からあなたに電話がありました。
This is very important
これはとても重要です
this is one of them
これはそのうちの 1 つです
So if the computer reads it, it will be placed in the five envelopes immediately.
したがって、コンピュータがそれを読み取ると、すぐに5つの封筒に入れられます。
that's enough for me
私にはそれで充分です
I'm short on time
時間がありません
I can only read a few
数枚しか読めない
I saw those five
その5人を見ました
can be dealt with immediately
すぐに対処できる
down may be a second tier
下は2層目かもしれない
third floor fourth floor
3階 4階
it can follow these
これらに従うことができます
your own way
自分のやり方で
Categorize this email
このメールを分類する
must go at this time
この時間に行かなければなりません
read that email content
そのメールの内容を読む
understand
理解
After understanding to a certain extent
ある程度理解した上で
There is no way to classify
分類する方法がない
There is also this automatic off-script recovery
この自動オフスクリプトリカバリもあります
There are many emails
メールがたくさんある
For example, ask you when
たとえば、「いつ」と尋ねます。
What kind of meeting can I have?
どのような打ち合わせができるのでしょうか？
wrote a lot
たくさん書いた
Finally there is a table
ついにテーブルが登場
let you lick right
正しく舐めさせてください
then you already have one
それならあなたはすでに持っています
Google's calendar is over there
Googleのカレンダーはあそこにあります
You are Google Calendar
あなたはGoogleカレンダーです
are you going to find it yourself?
自分で見つけるつもりですか？
Just tell the computer to find it yourself
自分で見つけるようにコンピューターに指示するだけです
See if I have time
時間があれば見てください
just fill it back
それを埋め戻すだけです
so later these
それで後でこれらを
is the appointment
予定です
It's just things like fixed grains.
まさに固定穀物のようなものです。
can be automatically read by computer
コンピューターで自動的に読み取ることができます
Automatic recovery
自動回復
don't need a secretary
秘書はいらない
This one is more difficult
こっちの方が難しいよ
automated scoring system
自動採点システム
Ministry of Science and Technology Program
科学技術省プログラム
Ministry of Science and Technology is now a year
科学技術省は1年になりました
There may be hundreds of thousands of plans
何十万もの計画があるかもしれない
go in
入る
This suggestion is not from me, but from the Executive Yuan
この提案は私からではなく、行政院からのものです。
A certain official said, he said it cost too much money
ある役人は「金がかかりすぎる」と言っていた。
Send a plan every time
毎回計画を送る
A plan needs to be sent to three people for review
計画はレビューのために 3 人に送信する必要があります
2000 yuan per person
1人あたり2000元
So a plan is six thousand
つまり計画は6000です
Those hundreds of thousands of projects add up to billions
これら数十万のプロジェクトは合計すると数十億に達します
This is the first trial and the deputy judge has not yet arrived. The deputy judge is
これは初公判で副判事はまだ到着していません。
It was also sent to some more famous scholars for review
この論文はさらに有名な学者にも査読のために送られました。
Is there any way for this to be like TOEFL composition?
これをTOEFLの作文のようにする方法はありますか？
automatic scoring
自動採点
TOEFL Essay Now Has Two Scores
TOEFL エッセイのスコアが 2 つになりました
One is a human call, the other is a computer call
1 つは人間の呼び出し、もう 1 つはコンピューターの呼び出しです
computer, because it is roughly divided into six levels
コンピューターは大きく6つのレベルに分かれているので、
six levels, it has had a lot of examples before
6 つのレベル、これまでに多くの例がありました
What kind of composition is at which level
どのレベルのどのような構成ですか
So now the computer can do a classification
これでコンピューターが分類できるようになりました
It's a new composition
新しい編成です
It puts you in the most likely tier
それはあなたを最も可能性の高い層に置きます
score decides
スコアが決める
If this score is similar to that of others
このスコアが他のスコアと似ている場合
it's over
終わりました
it saves a lot of effort
多くの労力を節約できます
about three percent
約3パーセント
95% of the cases are passed
95％のケースが通過します
There are a few 5% cases
5％程度のケースもある
If the scores are too far apart
スコアが離れすぎる場合
find someone else to fight
他に戦う相手を見つける
Just save Raleigh
ローリーを救ってあげてください
So the Ministry of Science and Technology plans to do the same?
それでは科学技術省も同様のことを計画しているのでしょうか？
province alone
州だけ
Then a computer saves
その後、コンピューターが保存します
then the score is very close
そうすればスコアは非常に近いです
Just pass
ただ通過してください
How many billions of dollars can this save the country?
これで何十億ドルが国を救えるでしょうか？
Then the essay province
それからエッセイ県
Papers we are now saving
現在保存している書類
Like all of our resources in a journal
ジャーナル内のすべてのリソースと同様に
English periodicals
英語の定期刊行物
1,000 papers submitted each year
毎年 1,000 件の論文が投稿される
In the end less than 5% were accepted
最終的に採用されたのは5％未満でした
95% were rejected
95%が拒否されました
Nor can the computer be used for a preliminary review
また、コンピュータを事前レビューに使用することもできません。
Don't even look at the 50%
50％すら見ないでください
you can reject
拒否できます
Write a very simple English is not fluent
非常に簡単な英語を書くのは流暢ではありません
or what kind of case
あるいはどのような場合ですか
He can read this
彼はこれを読むことができます
resume selection
選択を再開する
Now we have trouble finding a job
今私たちは仕事を見つけるのに苦労しています
resume to which company
どの会社への履歴書
The company picks up
会社が引き取ります
Like that big company, there are tens of thousands of letters
あの大企業みたいに何万通もの手紙がある
he can't read
彼は読めません
He wants to say there is a form
彼は形式があると言いたいのです
Then he uses that data base for everything
そして彼はそのデータベースをあらゆることに使用します
But most people don't like that
しかし、ほとんどの人はそれが好きではありません
OK, what about the rating systems?
さて、評価システムについてはどうですか?
most can use computer
ほとんどの人はコンピュータを使用できます
The same is true for recommendation systems, product recommendation
レコメンデーションシステムや商品レコメンデーションについても同様です。
Now you want to buy an air conditioner
今エアコンを買おうと思っています
What kind of form do you like?
どんな形が好きですか？
what is quiet or what
静かなのか何なのか
A lot of descriptions are finished
たくさんの説明が書かれています
they recommend you right away
彼らはすぐにあなたを勧めます
Then this recommendation system does not mean
それでは、この推薦制度は意味がありません。
The manufacturer said his air conditioner is very quiet
メーカーはエアコンがとても静かだと言いました
I went to many blogs to read
たくさんのブログを読みに行きました
Say what these people said about this air conditioner
このエアコンについてこの人たちが何と言ったか教えてください
collect him all
彼を全部集めて
Then hit a new score
そして新たなスコアを叩き出す
so it's very complicated
とても複雑です
this type of ad
このタイプの広告
future ads
今後の広告
We watch a lot of movies on that internet now
私たちは今、インターネットでたくさんの映画を見ています
In particular, many serial machines in mainland China have already been installed.
特に中国本土では多くのシリアル機が導入済みです。
He is not afraid of your computer now
彼は今ではあなたのコンピュータを恐れていません
Because you watch TV and watch commercials
テレビを見たりコマーシャルを見たりするからです。
The computer also sees advertisements
コンピューターにも広告が表示されます
So he thinks there is no difference
だから彼は違いがないと思っている
That part of the ad cannot be omitted
広告のその部分は省略できません
You can't press it no matter what
どうやっても押せないよ
he kept talking
彼は話し続けた
Now the advertisements are the same as those on TV, everyone sees the same advertisement
今では広告はテレビと同じになり、誰もが同じ広告を見ます
If he's smarter in the future, his ad, you've changed seasons recently and want to buy some clothes or your shoes are broken
彼が将来もっと賢くなったら、彼の広告、あなたは最近季節が変わり、服を買いたいと思っていますか、靴が壊れています
If he knows, he will put some things you really like, and the style is based on the shoes you bought before for a comparison
彼が知っていれば、あなたが本当に気に入っているものをいくつか入れて、スタイルは以前に比較のために購入した靴に基づいています
That ad, you saw it and immediately went out to buy it, or bought it online
その広告を見て、すぐに買いに行ったり、オンラインで購入したりしました
It is very meaningful to recommend
勧めることに大きな意味がある
Intelligent teaching assistant agent and health system
インテリジェントなティーチングアシスタントエージェントとヘルスシステム
IBM's WATCHEN is to push his entire system to Medical Science
IBM の WATCHEN は、システム全体を医療科学にプッシュする予定です
We are now talking about assistant teaching assistants. In fact, we did it a long time ago, but because we are not very smart
私たちは今、アシスタントティーチングアシスタントについて話しています。実際、私たちはずっと前にそれをやりましたが、私たちはあまり賢くないので、
So 24 hours is not used by so many people
つまり、24時間はそれほど多くの人が利用していない
Future teaching assistants, we just finished, have to be very smart
将来のティーチングアシスタントは、完成したばかりですが、非常に賢くなければなりません
Teaching assistant agent Math assistant agent
ティーチングアシスタントエージェント 数学アシスタントエージェント
If the elementary school mathematics just now
さっきの小学生の算数なら
you can get 90 points
90点を獲得できます
or 95 points
または95点
Everyone can be a teaching assistant
誰でもティーチングアシスタントになれる
but you also need to understand
しかし、理解する必要もあります
There is also a question answering system
質問応答システムもあります
Can understand the meaning of questions that students don't understand
生徒が理解できない質問の意味を理解できる
can help him explain
彼の説明を手伝うことができる
I think this is the greatest help for all children
これがすべての子供たちにとって最大の助けになると思います
English and Mathematics
英語と数学
This is medically related
これは医療関係です
it's big
それは大きいです
the university wrote a
大学が書きました
A description of a patient's condition
患者の状態の説明
Jennifer States
ジェニファー・ステイツ
what we have to do is
私たちがしなければならないことは
Computer poison to all Risk Factor
すべてのリスク要因に対するコンピューターの毒
remember it
それを覚えて
Then put all the Medication
それから薬をすべて入れます
he
他
what did the doctor prescribe
医者は何を処方しましたか
Or what medicine did he take to remember it
あるいはそれを思い出すために彼はどんな薬を服用しましたか
Then he went to do the quality of the health check
それから彼は健康診断の質を調べに行きました
pick him up
彼を迎えに行く
and put it in this
そしてこれに入れてください
Put it in and he will know
それを入れれば彼は分かるでしょう
What is Connected Risk Factor
接続されたリスク要因とは何ですか?
Medical Lyrical Minds, this business literature is growing very fast. Generally, reading or reading papers in many fields is very important, but not as important as Medical Science
Medical Lyrical Minds、このビジネス文献は急速に成長しています。一般に、多くの分野の論文を読んだり読んだりすることは非常に重要ですが、医学ほど重要ではありません
Because everyone in Medical Science knows why it screens out and seeks a higher level, because any one of it, such as doing a certain experiment on a veteran, will be of interest to everyone
なぜなら、医学界の誰もが、なぜそれがふるいにかけられ、より高いレベルを求めるのかを知っているからです。退役軍人に対して特定の実験を行うなど、そのどれもが全員の興味を引くからです。
Because it wants to know whether it will have a similar effect if the same experiment is done on humans, so its broadness is very strong
同じ実験を人体に行った場合に同様の効果があるかどうかを知りたいため、その幅が非常に強い
You can’t do it in computer science. If you read the paper in your field in the field of computer science, you probably can’t make a mistake. You can’t understand other things if you want to read them.
「コンピュータサイエンスでは無理です。コンピュータサイエンスの分野の論文を読めば、おそらく間違っていないでしょう。他のことは読みたくても理解できません。」
As for this aspect, so Medical Science they often say that I have a problem and I want the computer to help me find it. Now if I use Google, it returns tens of thousands of tablets every time.
この側面に関しては、医学分野では、「問題があるので、コンピュータに問題を見つけてもらいたい」とよく言われますが、現在、Google を使用すると、毎回何万台ものタブレットが返されます。
Generally speaking, when we search on Google, it doesn’t matter if there are tens of thousands of pieces, because the first ten probably have what I want, bye
一般的に言えば、Google で検索するときは、何万個の項目があっても問題ではありません。最初の 10 個には、おそらく私の欲しいものが含まれているからです。
For example, you need to know which genes are related to a certain disease
たとえば、どの遺伝子が特定の病気に関連しているかを知る必要があります。
This may really require hundreds of thousands of papers to read
これには実際に何十万もの論文を読む必要があるかもしれません
Then there are some sentences in him saying that this is very helpful for something
そして、彼の中には、これは何かに非常に役立つという文章がいくつかあります。
You really have to read every sentence.
本当にすべての文を読まなければなりません。
So the answer to this kind of question is very difficult.
したがって、この種の質問に対する答えは非常に困難です。
Gene-to-Gene Interactions
遺伝子間の相互作用
And cancer patients, genetic mutations, and methods of diagnosis and treatment
がん患者、遺伝子変異、診断と治療の方法
People who are sick are very careful
病気の人は細心の注意を払っています
can you read soon
すぐに読めますか
These papers related to him
彼に関連したこれらの論文
Also, what the President of the United States is promoting is not presuci medicine
また、アメリカ大統領が推進しているのは前出医学ではありません。
It's Personalized Medicine
それは個別化医療です
How to collect these data
これらのデータを収集する方法
How to do a comparison with your genes
自分の遺伝子と比較する方法
It has something to do with the above problems
それは上記の問題と関係があります
so the answer to any question
だからどんな質問にも答えられる
It may involve really reading so many papers
本当にたくさんの論文を読む必要があるかもしれない
It is impossible to have this manpower now
今この人材を確保するのは不可能です
impossible in the future
将来的には不可能
So this aspect requires the help of a computer.
したがって、この側面ではコンピューターの助けが必要です。
So life scientists need a comparison
したがって、生命科学者には比較が必要です
has a hundred times more searches
検索数は 100 倍
Here is the end
ここで終わりです
This has something to do with your work
これはあなたの仕事と関係があります
What does the next issue have to do with doing things?
次の問題は、物事を行うこととどのような関係がありますか?
let's talk first
まずは話しましょう
In fact, many things in society are now hierarchically responsible.
実際、社会の多くの事柄は現在、階層的に責任を負っています。
because you called the travel agency
旅行代理店に電話したから
Said that I want to go to Pupu Island or Green Island
ププ島かグリーン島に行きたいって言ってた
Or to Orchid Island
あるいは蘭嶼へ
he has not been to these places
彼はこれらの場所に行ったことがない
but there are other people beside him
でも彼の隣には他の人がいる
or someone from another company
または別の会社の人
He can help you collect information
彼は情報収集を手伝ってくれます
tell you what's the fun
何が楽しいのか教えてください
It's up to you to decide whether to go to this place
この場所に行きたいかどうかはあなたが決めます
When is there a big inspection
大規模な検査はいつありますか
what temperature
気温は何度ですか
Many things are in charge of different people
多くのことを別の人が担当する
So each class works
したがって、各クラスは機能します
data collection
データ収集
Decide how the next level of work will be organized
次のレベルの作業をどのように組織するかを決定する
can do it well
上手にできる
If all levels make coordinated decisions
すべてのレベルが調整された意思決定を行う場合
Complete work can go smoothly
完成した作業がスムーズに進みます
that means
つまり
If the following are all robots
以下がすべてロボットの場合
this is all your work left
これがあなたの仕事の残りすべてです
the coordination and decision making
調整と意思決定
if your job
あなたの仕事なら
You can also use the code name of the machine, you don't need to exist
マシンのコード名を使用することもできます。存在する必要はありません。
so this is troublesome
だからこれは面倒だ
so why is it like playing chess
ではなぜチェスをしているようなものなのか
Our every decision-making process is very similar to playing chess
私たちのあらゆる意思決定プロセスはチェスをプレイすることに非常に似ています
it's your son
それはあなたの息子です
The opponent may play this one
相手はこれをプレイしてもよい
or go somewhere else
それともどこか別の場所に行きますか
So how many steps do you have to consider
それで、どれくらいのステップを考慮する必要がありますか
It's possible that if he gets down here
彼がここに降り立ったら、おそらくそうなるだろう
You go to another place in the second step
2番目のステップでは別の場所に移動します
third step
第三段階
is the step you have to consider
考慮する必要があるステップです
what's your final decision
最終的な決断は何ですか
So it's very similar to playing chess
つまり、チェスをプレイするのと非常に似ています
If you do this every step
これを各ステップごとに行うと、
have an agent
エージェントがいる
agent machine talk to you
エージェントマシンがあなたに話しかけます
If you take this step
この一歩を踏み出せば
what is his likely success rate
彼の成功率はどのくらいでしょうか
Then such words
するとそんな言葉が
you can make a decision soon
あなたはすぐに決断を下すことができます
But if there are so many machines
でも、機械がたくさんあると、
your job to decide
決めるのはあなたの仕事
will be replaced by robots
ロボットに取って代わられるだろう
So it's slowly
それではゆっくりです
we are bottom up
私たちはボトムアップです
OK, parameter setting of the biological laboratory
OK、生物学実験室のパラメータ設定
Which combination should be tried first
どの組み合わせを最初に試すべきか
that one is the second try
あれは2回目の試みです
You want the computer to make a list
コンピュータにリストを作ってもらいたい
Then you just have to make a choice
あとは選択するだけです
Then if he has the ability
それで彼に能力があれば
Maybe one day he'll tell you
たぶんいつか彼はあなたに言うでしょう
I've helped you choose the best for this role
この役割に最適なものを選択するのをお手伝いしました
Well, he doesn't need you at all
まあ、彼はあなたをまったく必要としていません
That is to say, in many experiments
つまり、多くの実験では
If he can automate later
後で自動化できれば
Then we really don’t need to do dry lab today
それなら今日はドライラボをする必要はありません
Because we told the computer to try it out
コンピューターに試してみるよう指示したからです
Replace this parameter with that one and run out
このパラメータをそのパラメータに置き換えて実行します
he may have to run for a day or two
彼は1日か2日走らなければならないかもしれない
If you say this action, the computer will do it
このアクションを言うとコンピューターが実行します
He can help you to try different parameters
さまざまなパラメータを試すのを手伝ってくれます
If the computer is fast enough
コンピューターが十分に速い場合
These things can be done right now
これらのことは今すぐにでも実行できます
Discussion on research direction
研究の方向性についてのディスカッション
What method is used which one comes first and which one comes after
どのようなメソッドが使用されるか、どれが最初でどれが後に来るか
depth first
深さ優先
Go down in depth first
まずは深く掘り下げていきます
Breadth first go sideways
幅はまず横に進みます
Law of success
成功劇律
So now all we need is to say
だから今私たちが必要としているのはこう言うことだけです
Not a single computer can help us anytime soon
すぐに私たちを助けてくれるコンピューターは 1 台もありません
Calculate these laws of success
成功の法則を計算してみよう
Now in many fields, like in the field of FanX show, they may have it, because he has a lot of data, he can estimate what will happen if you invest in US dollars now
現在、FanX ショーの分野など、多くの分野で、彼らはそれを持っているかもしれません。彼は多くのデータを持っているため、今米ドルに投資すると何が起こるかを推定できます。
The price of the US dollar has risen in the past two days, should I buy it immediately, or buy it in two days, how to do things in Changhua, how to learn
過去 2 日間で米ドルの価格が上昇しました。すぐに購入すべきか、2 日以内に購入すべきか、彰化での活動方法、学習方法
The same is true for this. Didn’t we talk about text comprehension just now?
これも同様で、先ほど文章理解について話しましたよね？
This computer learns a lot, he can also write, because those sentences come and go, he can add one, but although he can add everything, there is nothing difficult
このコンピュータは多くのことを学び、文章を書くこともできます。文章が行き来するので、何かを追加することもできますが、すべてを追加することはできますが、難しいことは何もありません
In the future, speeches will be relatively simple, that is, I will write the first few sheets for him to prepare for the exam.
将来的には、スピーチは比較的単純なものになるでしょう。つまり、試験の準備のために最初の数枚を私が彼に書くことになります。
As we said earlier, the exam bot is already preparing the email
前に述べたように、試験ボットはすでにメールを準備しています。
The last one is which jobs are easily replaced by robots, which are low-level agent jobs
最後の項目は、どのジョブがロボットに簡単に置き換えられるかです。これは低レベルのエージェントのジョブです。
So everyone, think about it, if you are about to enter the workplace now, I often tell master students, don't think trivial things
だから皆さん、考えてみてください。これから職場に入ろうとしている人は、修士課程の学生によく言います、小さなことを考えるな
high salary now
今では給料が高い
when you turn 40
40歳になったら
How much more powerful was the computer than you at that time
当時のコンピュータはあなたよりどれくらい強力でしたか
Many people face this choice at the age of 30 or 40
多くの人は30歳か40歳でこの選択に直面します
Say he wants to change the line
彼がラインを変更したいと言う
Because of his line of work, he is already weaker than the newcomers
職業柄、すでに新人より弱い
Now it is compared with people and later it will be compared with computers
今は人間と比較されていますが、後にはコンピュータと比較されるでしょう。
The work content is simple and repetitive
仕事内容は単純作業の繰り返しです
like a factory without lights
明かりのない工場みたいに
I don't need anyone anymore
もう誰も必要ない
simple customer service questions
カスタマーサービスの簡単な質問
read simple script
簡単なスクリプトを読む
These DTLs are quick to do
これらの DTL はすぐに実行できます
The most complex part of every job is still handled by someone
すべての仕事の最も複雑な部分は依然として誰かによって処理されます
But there are fewer and fewer people to hire
でも雇える人はどんどん減っていきます
we just said
私たちは今言いました
For example, there may only be 20% of difficult questions in customer service questions
たとえば、カスタマー サービスの質問には難しい質問が 20% しかない可能性があります。
need real people to answer
本物の人に答えてもらう必要がある
But other words don't need
でも他の言葉は必要ない
So like now many banks have more than 200 customer service
現在のように、多くの銀行には 200 以上の顧客サービスがあります
in a few years
数年で
We are now going to help banks build an automated answering system
私たちは今後、銀行による自動応答システムの構築を支援していきます。
After a few years, he may only need 50, 20 customer service
数年後には、50、20 件の顧客サービスしか必要としないかもしれません
real people are answering
本物の人々が答えています
Because simple problems are already
簡単な問題はすでに終わっているので、
What Google Designs Now
Google現在設計的信仰
Because Google says you type in a question
Googleは質問を入力すると言うので
It answers in 0.4 seconds after writing on it
書いてから0.4秒で応答
In fact, your question has already been asked
実際、あなたの質問はすでに行われています
It only needs to search in front of that
その前を検索するだけで済みます
How did you shoot this question?
どうやってこの質問を打ったのですか？
It doesn't need to re-find it for you
再検索する必要はありません
So 90% of the questions are already asked
つまり、質問の 90% はすでに出題されています
That's what we call an FAQ
それが FAQ と呼ばれるものです
no need to search anymore
もう探す必要はありません
The most complex part of every job needs you to deal with
すべての仕事の中で最も複雑な部分に対処する必要があります
But if this complexity
しかし、この複雑さであれば、
What kind of complexity are we looking at
私たちが注目しているのはどのような複雑さですか
If its complexity is only because it has too many possibilities
もしその複雑さが単に可能性が多すぎるからだとしたら
Or you have trouble explaining to it
あるいは、それを説明するのが難しい
might as well do it yourself
自分でやってもいいかもしれない
In this way, the computer in the future will be faster
このようにして、将来のコンピュータはより高速になります
like we just said
先ほど言ったように
You have to run for a day or two with any set of parameters
パラメータを設定して 1 ～ 2 日実行する必要があります
In the future, the computer may run out for a minute or two
将来的には、コンピューターが 1 ～ 2 分間機能しなくなる可能性があります。
this is no joke
これは冗談ではありません
It's very likely a minute or two to run out
1、2分でなくなる可能性が非常に高い
You can quickly think, you help me run these 100 kinds of parameter groups
あなたはこれら 100 種類のパラメータ グループの実行を手伝ってくれるとすぐに考えることができます。
Then, after he understands your words, he will run away by himself in the future
そして、彼はあなたの言葉を理解した後、将来一人で逃げるでしょう
He doesn't need you, if he is more considerate, everyone can gradually automate these
彼はあなたを必要としていません、もし彼がもっと思いやりを持っていたら、誰もがこれらのことを徐々に自動化できるでしょう
So if what a master student does is to try out different possibilities
修士課程の学生がさまざまな可能性を試すことだとしたら、
But the teacher will tell him a direction, which is more difficult
でも先生は彼に方向性を教えるでしょう、それはもっと難しいです
But if the computer can understand this direction, then the necessity of this master's existence will also be reduced
しかし、コンピュータがこの方向性を理解できれば、このマスターの存在の必要性も減ります。
So in the end machines will replace people faster and faster
つまり、最終的には機械が人間に取って代わる速度がどんどん速くなるのです
Below what we just talked about, he ran up from that button
私たちが今話したことの下で、彼はそのボタンから駆け上がった
What we are seeing now is the manufacturing industry, they are talking about one case at a time
私たちが今見ているのは製造業であり、彼らは一度に 1 つのケースについて話しています。
The implementation started last year, and many factories immediately bought more than 1,000 robots
導入は昨年始まり、多くの工場がすぐに 1,000 台以上のロボットを購入しました
Because the degree of automation in the manufacturing industry is already very high
製造業における自動化の度合いはすでに非常に高いため、
Now it's the same in the office
今はオフィスでも同じです
If our secretary asks for too much leave every day, he will take this
もし私たちの秘書が毎日あまりにも多くの休暇を要求したら、彼はこれを取得するでしょう
This secretary machine has been introduced
この秘書機が導入されました
Ingredient designer if moody day and night
成分デザイナーが昼も夜も気分が高ければ
Low-level composition design is completely done by computer
低レベルの構成設計はすべてコンピュータで行われます
24 hours is scary
24時間って怖いですね
and he's very fast
そして彼はとても速いです
simple assistant
単純なアシスタント
This is a teacher I just talked about
こちらは先ほどお話しした先生です
Also watch out
こちらも気をつけてね
Because there are so many good teaching materials on the Internet
インターネット上には良い教材がたくさんあるので、
are taught by very famous teachers.
とても有名な先生が教えてくれます。
The only inconvenience is when you say you don't understand
唯一不便なのは、あなたが理解できないと言ったときです
he won't tell you
彼はあなたに教えてくれません
If he had a teacher today with a question answering system next to
もし今日、質問応答システムを備えた先生が隣にいたら
a teaching assistant
ティーチングアシスタント
You don't understand, stop him and ask the teaching assistant
理解できないなら、彼を止めてティーチングアシスタントに尋ねてください
what did that sentence mean
その文はどういう意味でしたか
words he understands
彼が理解できる言葉
Does this person still need to go to school?
この人はまだ学校に行く必要がありますか?
The best teacher in the world has been recorded
世界で最高の教師が記録されました
The best teaching assistants are by your side to help you answer questions
最高のティーチングアシスタントがあなたのそばにいて、質問に答えます。
In this case
この場合
many teachers work
多くの教師が働いています
Like teaching elementary school books, if you have to talk about it, you don’t have to teach it.
小学校の本を教えるのと同じで、講義があれば教える必要はない。
because you can only teach one hour a day
1日1時間しか教えられないから
That computer is available 24 hours a day
そのコンピュータは 24 時間使用可能です
no way to compare with him
彼と比べようがない
so it's very dangerous
だからとても危険です
assistant too
アシスタントも
I'm talking about research assistants
研究助手について話しているのですが
A lot of things for research assistants are highly repetitive
研究助手にとって多くのことは非常に反復的です
the more this kind of thing
こういう事が多ければ多いほど
you have to be more careful
もっと気をつけなければなりません
I can write a sincere story later
真面目な話は後で書ける
Please write a sincere story and replace yourself
誠実な話を書いて自分に代わってください
This is actually happening
これは実際に起こっていることです
no one did it on purpose
誰も故意にやったわけではない
that is
あれは
Because what he does is too monotonous
彼のやることは単調すぎるから
He doesn't like doing it either, right?
彼もそれをするのが好きではありませんよね？
Then he will write a truth instead
そうすれば彼は代わりに真実を書くだろう
So slowly these jobs will be replaced by machines
とてもゆっくりと、これらの仕事は機械に取って代わられるでしょう
That's all for today's speech
今日のスピーチは以上です
thank you
ありがとう
Thank you, Director Xu, for your wonderful speech.
徐所長、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました。
so we probably still have some time to come
だからまだ時間はあるだろう
Let everyone be open to ask questions
誰でも気軽に質問できるようにする
good here
ここでいいです
Press the front microphone
フロントマイクを押します
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
I am interested and want to ask more
興味があるので詳しく聞きたい
It lies in the Principle-based approach mentioned by the teacher just now
それは先ほど先生がおっしゃった原理主義にあります。
But like, for example, I just gave a few examples
しかし、今挙げた例のように
It seems to be a bunch of similar things
似たようなのがいっぱいあるような気がする
Actively seek out a Principle
積極的に原則を探求する
and make things faster and better
物事をより速く、より良くする
But I remember the Mathematics Institute of Academia Sinica
しかし、私は中央研究院数学研究所を覚えています。
The Journal of Mathematical Communication has been talking about one thing for a while now
Journal of Mathematical Communication は、しばらくの間、あることについて話し続けています。
That is to say, the Western period
つまり西洋時代
It seems to be able to notice that there is a similarity with arithmetic
算数との類似点があることに気づくことができそうです
It's the spirit of learning mathematics
それは数学を学ぶ精神です
People who go up and down are better
上がったり下がったりする人の方が良い
The more he seems to be able to raise his point of view
彼は自分の視点を高めることができるようであればあるほど、
So the teacher's Principle-based approach
つまり、教師の原則に基づいたアプローチは、
When the computer formulates these Principles
コンピュータがこれらの原則を定式化するとき
Is there any way for him to raise or lower his level
彼のレベルを上げたり下げたりする方法はありますか
In other words, is there a way for him to say
言い換えれば、彼にこう言う方法はありますか？
From only being able to see whether the reference is right or wrong
参照が正しいか間違っているかだけを確認できることから
into a paper
紙に
Does he lack Principle
彼には原則が欠けているのだろうか
Or is there a way for him to
それとも彼にできる方法はあるのでしょうか？
I know a person makes a typo in a sentence
ある人が文の中でタイプミスをしていることを私は知っています
Become a person who knows that he will not look at the four lines and say the wrong thing
4行を見て間違ったことを言わないとわかる人になれ
So your Principals are all parallel?
つまり、プリンシパルはすべて並列ですか?
Or can he see the Principals of different classes from top to bottom?
それとも、さまざまなクラスの校長を上から下まで見ることができますか?
This question is very knowledgeable
この質問は非常に知識が豊富です
It's just that some people may not hear clearly
ただ、人によってははっきりと聞こえない場合があります
That is to say, when you study, you acquire the superficial knowledge.
つまり、勉強すると表面的な知識が身につくのです。
Or you can learn more abstract
あるいは、より抽象的なことを学ぶこともできます
In fact, computers need to learn abstract knowledge
実際、コンピュータは抽象的な知識を学習する必要があります
not difficult
難しくない
because of U.S
米国のせいで
especially since we've done a lot of this kind of speech analysis
特に私たちはこの種の音声分析をたくさん行ってきたので
So every word has its upper position
したがって、すべての単語には上位の位置があります
more superior
より優れた
like that
そのように
Banana right?
バナナですよね？
it is a fruit
それは果物です
Another what to eat
もう一つ何を食べるか
then we are all done
それで終わりです
so
それで
Today I learned a Pattern
今日はパターンを学びました
I can ginarize it to a higher level immediately
すぐに高いレベルにジナライズできます
not its original word
本来の言葉ではない
that this
これは
In this relatively high Pattern
この比較的高いパターンでは
fits a lot
たくさんフィットします
At this time, it is equivalent to saying
このとき、次のように言うのと同じです。
I can use it elsewhere
他でも使えるよ
so next time you put this
それで、次にこれを置くときは
There will be no problem changing orange apple
オレンジリンゴを変更しても問題ありません
This is absolutely no problem
これはまったく問題ありません
Thanks
ありがとう
ok there's someone over there
わかった、あそこに誰かいるよ
Want to know more about that
それについてもっと知りたい
PBA seems to be able to understand some semantics
PBA はいくつかのセマンティクスを理解できるようです
green
緑
That is, PBA seems to understand some semantics
つまり、PBA はいくつかのセマンティクスを理解しているようです
Is it possible that it produces
それが生み出す可能性はあるのでしょうか？
that is to say the writing part
つまり書く部分です
Use the PBA way to generate some of that
PBA の方法を使用してその一部を生成します
that's easy because
それは簡単です、なぜなら
you think it's the other way around
あなたはそれが逆だと思いますか
I just didn't give an example to say
だから例を挙げて言わなかったんだ
How would you describe the distance between two points
2 点間の距離をどのように説明しますか
Is the distance between the two places correct?
2 つの場所間の距離は正しいですか?
Then you collect such tools
それから、そのようなツールを集めます
next time i ask you to talk
今度話してもらいます
you take one of you
あなたはあなたのどちらかを連れて行きます
Pick it out and talk it out and it's over
選んで話し合えば終わりです
So its absorption and production are the same thing
したがって、その吸収と生成は同じことです
the same thing
同一回事
Then its sentence pattern means
すると、その文型は、
I change it here
ここで変更します
what is this noun
この名詞は何ですか
What is that noun replaced with?
その名詞は何に置き換えられますか?
it can have another meaning
別の意味もあるかもしれない
this too
これも
You can go backwards from the process of learning it
学ぶ過程から遡ることができる
still have a question
まだ質問があります
that joke
その冗談
That's the one
それだ
like in Chinese
中国語のように
Just use the PBI method
PBI メソッドを使用するだけです
Approximately how many Principals are there?
校長は大体何人くらいいますか？
Can let the machine understand Chinese
機械に中国語を理解させることができる
what about other languages
他の言語はどうですか
this really needs to be understood
これは本当に理解する必要があります
Because there are so many Principals
校長がたくさんいるので、
speak like we do
私たちと同じように話す
when we were checking restaurants
レストランをチェックしていたとき
will anyone speak
誰か話しますか
I have a friend
友達がいます
like to drink
飲むのが好き
which restaurant is suitable
どのレストランが適していますか
he talked for a long time
彼は長い間話しました
just looking for a place to drink
ただ飲む場所を探しているだけです
If you need to understand this sentence
この文を理解する必要がある場合
how many different ways
いくつの異なる方法があるか
Can be mapped to
にマッピングできます
can like to drink
飲むのが好きかもしれない
this is
これは
Benefits of Big Data
ビッグデータの利点
I can be online today
今日はオンラインになれます
collect a lot of sentences like these
このような文をたくさん集めてください
i know i like to drink
私がお酒を飲むのが好きだと知っています
How many different ways are there
さまざまな方法が何通りあるのか
I can filter it out
フィルターで除去できるよ
i am this one
私はこれです
Map
地図
You can't do that with Dibnurin
ディブヌリンではそれができない
Because the expression of so-called meaning is human assign
いわゆる意味の表現は人間が割り当てたものだから
There is no saving energy on this aspect.
この点ではエネルギーの節約はできません。
But you only need to collect this information
ただし、この情報を収集するだけで十分です
Our principle can be learned immediately
私たちの理念はすぐに学べます
I don't know if this answers your question
これがあなたの質問の答えになるかどうかわかりません
I can explain it with PPA
PPAで説明できるよ
The complexity is similar across languages
複雑さはどの言語でも同様です
Its PPA has nothing to do with the language
その PPA は言語とは何の関係もありません
is your grammar or something
あなたの文法か何かですか
Your pattern itself already contains
パターン自体にはすでに含まれています
so it doesn't matter how your grammar is
だから文法がどうであれ関係ない
It can even learn your grammar
文法も学習できます
For example, English verb singular plus S something
たとえば、英語の動詞単数プラス S 何か
It can learn those things by itself
それらのことを自分で学習できる
So it has the benefit of that law
つまり、その法律の恩恵を受けるのです
It also has statistical calculation capabilities for this type of insertion deletion
この種の挿入削除に対する統計計算機能も備えています。
ok, the gentleman in the back
オーケー、後ろにいる紳士
Teacher Qiu
キウ先生
Just now you mentioned that
今、あなたはそれを言いましたね
People are talking about many conditions in the province
人々は州のさまざまな状況について話しています
right
右
people in different situations
さまざまな状況にある人々
He can understand what you mean by planning
彼はあなたが計画するということが何を意味するのか理解できます
But in the opposite direction, you can tell the machine to write a novel
しかし逆に、機械に小説を書くように命令することもできます。
he is equivalent to
彼はと同等です
because people have imagination
人には想像力があるから
Then he can also imagine many conditions
そうすれば、彼は多くの状況を想像することもできます
like when the teacher mentioned
先生が言ったときのように
Taipei Taichung
台北 台中
In front he is selling tickets
前でチケットを売っている
you want to buy a ticket
チケットを買いたいですか
But just write Taipei Taichung
でも、台北、台中とだけ書いてください。
This machine can imagine
この機械は想像できる
what's in taipei
台北には何がありますか
what's in taichung
台中には何がありますか
Immediately afterwards he wrote a novel
その直後に彼は小説を書いた
He went to Taipei to Taichung to play
彼は台北から台中に遊びに行きました
meet someone
誰かに会う
who are you in love with
あなたは誰に恋をしていますか
a lot of them all come out
それらの多くはすべて出てきます
Is it possible to write a novel
小説を書くことは可能ですか
He inversely creates situations for himself
彼は逆に自分自身のために状況を作り出します
we talked about this
私たちはこれについて話しました
that is
あれは
You just have to teach him something
あなたは彼に何かを教えなければなりません
he can have a similar effect
彼にも同様の効果があるかもしれない
this is possible
これは可能です
if you give him a lot of this novel
この小説を彼にたくさんあげたら
he will read love novels
彼は恋愛小説を読むでしょう
different from the other one, what happened first and what happened later
他のものとの違い、最初に何が起こったのか、何が後に起こったのか
After he remembers these things
彼がこれらのことを思い出した後、
He has another Principle Base to remember these
彼にはこれらを思い出すための別の原則基盤があります
Then things with similarities and minor differences will be regenerated by him.
そして、類似点と小さな相違点を持つものは彼によって再生されます。
For example, when we write a letter of introduction
たとえば、紹介状を書くとき
We usually say that the student is very hardworking
私たちはよく「その学生はとても勤勉だ」と言いますが、
But he's not the smartest, we don't speak negatively
でも彼は最も賢いわけではない、私たちは否定的なことは言わない
we will turn around, right?
振り向くでしょう？
From work to business, I talked for a long time
仕事からビジネスまで、長い時間話しました
You can tell that he's not that smart
彼はそれほど賢くないことがわかります
In this sentence, this sequence can be handed over to the computer
この文では、このシーケンスをコンピュータに渡すことができます
you mark a lot of paragraphs like this
このように多くの段落にマークを付けます
Tell him that's a description that says he's hardworking, but not the smartest
それは彼が勤勉であるが、最も賢いわけではないという説明であると彼に伝えてください
5 percent, 10 percent, 20 percent than what we marked
私たちがマークしたものより 5 パーセント、10 パーセント、20 パーセント
He'll learn how to talk about five percent in the future
彼は将来、5パーセントについて話す方法を学ぶでしょう
How do you say twenty percent ten percent
20パーセント10パーセントってなんて言うの？
so this is possible
だからこれは可能です
But the front needs people to meet this standard
しかし、人々はこの基準を満たす必要があります
if he has the ability
彼に能力があるなら
right
右
assume an architect
建築家だと仮定して
Others have a piece of land
他の人は土地を持っています
the style he wants to cover
彼がカバーしたいスタイル
almost a thousand kinds
ほぼ千種類
that in this case
それはこの場合
Can the machine also
機械でもできますか
lots of imagination
たくさんの想像力
I use this pattern to give him
私はこのパターンを使って彼にプレゼントします
build this
これを構築します
what flavor is he
彼は何味ですか
what personality does he fit
彼はどのような性格に当てはまりますか
he almost
彼はほとんど
let the architect to some extent
ある程度は建築家に任せる
He said you design 100
彼はあなたが100をデザインすると言った
Then when he picked the third
それから彼が3番目を選んだとき
actually i think
実際私は思う
you are right
あなたが正しいです
today we
今日は私達
machine can't do
機械にはできない
It's because we humans don't know how to teach him
それは私たち人間が彼に教える方法を知らないからです
because we're kind of like
私たちは似ているから
Teach a cram student
塾生に教える
only one inside
中には1つだけ
is the computer
コンピューターです
if i could teach
私が教えることができたら
his ability to abstract
彼の抽象化能力
will be very strong
とても強いでしょう
so because
だから
i won't abstract the way
方法を抽象化しません
to teach this student
この生徒に教えるために
So he has no way to generalize
だから彼には一般化する方法がない
if i will
もしそうするなら
Actually this
実はこれ
you want him to generalize
あなたは彼に一般化してもらいたいのですか
like i think say
私が言うように
popular songs now
今人気の曲
listen carefully
注意深く耳を傾ける
his kind though
彼の種類だけど
not exactly the same
全く同じではない
but very heavy
しかしとても重い
There are several inflections
いくつかの曲がりがあります
If the computer memorizes this pattern
このパターンをコンピュータが記憶していれば
it will write a similar
同様のことを書きます
especially when we talk about
特に私たちがそれについて話すとき
Said that there are many dance songs in Korea that are well written
韓国にはよくできたダンスソングがたくさんあると言った
Then I learn a bit and I can make one myself
それから少し学んで自分でも作れるようにします
And it's guaranteed to be different
そしてそれは違うことが保証されています
no way to sue me
私を訴える方法はありません
So things like this are possible in the future
つまり、将来的にはこのようなことが可能になるのです
just say now
今言ってください
the hard part is saying
難しいのは言うことです
We haven't caught that expression yet.
私たちはまだその表現を捉えていません。
if caught
捕まった場合
It will be much easier than image recognition
画像認識よりもはるかに簡単になります
ok over there thanks
わかりました、ありがとう
very good speech
とても良いスピーチ
I bought a book about this two years ago
2年前にこれに関する本を買いました
called "how to speed"
いわゆる「スピードの出し方」
not line by line
一行ずつではない
speed
速度
I read half of the book and still don't understand
本を半分まで読んだのですが、まだ理解できません
Later I understood that you are looking for the pattern
後で、あなたがパターンを探していることが分かりました
right
右
right? just say
そうですか？言ってください
It gives you a square and you go find the pattern
それはあなたに正方形を与え、あなたはパターンを見つけに行きます
That's because you already have some
それはあなたがすでにいくつか持っているからです
So you know what it means when you see those words
だから、その言葉を見れば意味がわかる
This is a bit like what you just said
これはあなたが今言ったことと少し似ています
Your reference is to use one dimensional
参照は 1 次元を使用することです
is a series
シリーズです
Now it's impossible to read this like you said
今、あなたが言ったようにこれを読むことは不可能です
business book like
ビジネス本のような
Also go to find the pattern in this text
このテキストのパターンも探してください
So it's like saying look at everyone
だからみんなを見ろと言っているようなものだ
This Chinese has a former dean named Sony Chen
この中国人にはソニー・チェンという名前の元学部長がいる
It doesn't matter if he goes to bed at 3 o'clock all day and half sleeps
一日中3時に寝ても半分寝ても問題ない
but he asks questions
しかし彼は質問します
I think he also found a pattern
彼もパターンを見つけたと思う
is he knows him
彼は彼を知っていますか
Halfway through your talk, he already knows about other things.
あなたの話の途中で、彼はすでに他のことについて知っています。
So he has already decided the question
つまり、彼はすでに質問を決めています
So in general, this is the pattern
だからそのパターンだよ
Will not become two dimensional
二次元にならない
To become something else is for him to sporadically find out some
何か別のものになるということは、彼にとって何かを散発的に見つけることだ
law
法
Is this right with Xiaoxiang?
Xiaoxiangはそうですか？
In fact, part of
実際、その一部は、
This is actually
これは実際には
With the basic ability of the computer
パソコンの基本的な能力があれば、
to make this change
この変更を行うには
it's very easy to tell him
彼に言うのはとても簡単です
The difference now is that the understanding of basic things is not enough
今と違うのは、基本的なことの理解が十分ではないということです
So I'm assuming he's improving so fast
だから彼はとても早く上達していると思うよ
He will improve by leaps and bounds after reaching a level
あるレベルに到達すると、彼は飛躍的に向上します
so you said
それであなたは言いました
write a story what?
物語を書く、何？
are very likely
可能性が非常に高い
And there will be quite a bit of exclusivity
そしてかなりの独占性があるでしょう
Tasteful experience
味わい深い体験
that is
あれは
not casually
何気なくではなく
good over there
あそこはいいよ
To tell you the truth, I'm also an information
実を言うと、私も情報を求めています。
But learn for you on the screen
ただし、画面上で学習できます
No no
いやいや
I feel like
のような気がする
Because of the problem just mentioned
先ほど述べた問題のせいで
is his relevance
彼の関連性は
Then we put it from the original system
次に、元のシステムからそれを配置します
You do regular system analysis first
まず定期的にシステム分析を行います
analysis becomes structure
分析が構造になる
The structure will later become Majiu and become a block
構造物は後にマジウとなりブロックとなる
right
右
slowly become
ゆっくりとなる
he will become a parameter
彼はパラメータになるだろう
On the top
最上面
A parameter structure has
パラメータ構造には、
Now the other sea and air joint defense is our anti-fat gallbladder
さて、もう一つの海と空の共同防衛は、私たちの抗脂肪胆嚢です
That is the whole from the satellite to the bottom
それは衛星から下までの全体です
is also an enterprise architecture
エンタープライズアーキテクチャでもあります
Enterprise Architecture
エンタープライズアーキテクチャ
It is also doing the whole structure integration
全体の構造統合も行っています
That architecture has reasoning
そのアーキテクチャには理由がある
Now I'm doing something with some friends
今、友達数人と何かやってます
that is
あれは
In this way, some parts may need to be consulted with you
このように、一部の部分についてはお客様にご相談いただく必要がある場合がございます。
can help
助けられる
at this
この時点で
We can wait for this and we are off the market
これを待てば市場から消えます
It's okay, I just said something
大丈夫、ちょっと言いましたよ
It's on the Buddhist scriptures
仏教の経典に載ってますよ
It's just too complicated, repetitive scenes and characters appear
複雑すぎる、繰り返しのシーンやキャラクターが登場する
In fact, several parameters are extracted from it.
実際、そこからいくつかのパラメータが抽出されます。
over here
ここに
structure we already have
すでにある構造
Then these screened parts
次に、これらのスクリーンされた部分
and for example
そして例えば
More than 100 Buddhist medium personalities
100名以上の仏教霊媒師
Then each individual element
次に、個々の要素
I'll ask you later
後で聞いてみます
can you use this to help
これを使って助けてもらえますか
So this is how to refine Buddhist scriptures into
これが仏教経典を次のように洗練する方法です。
For example, it is a copy of Uncle Si
たとえば、Uncle Si のコピーです。
a bible ist
聖書です
can refine him
彼を磨くことができる
Ben has been good for so many years
ベンは何年も元気だった
everyone speak one
全員が一つ話します
You explain me and I don't understand until now
説明してもらっても今まで理解できなかった
In fact, it is found that the structure is quite clear
実際、その構造は非常に明確であることがわかります。
that time here
その時はここで
it's absolutely possible
それは絶対に可能です
right now we
今、私たちは
One of the things they did to help the food and clothing store was to put
食料品店と衣料品店を助けるために彼らが行ったことの 1 つは、
Earlier
以前的
What is that twenty forty?
その240は何ですか？
All these people, officials and civilians inside, what?
中には役人も民間人もいるのに、何だ？
find all the horizon
すべての地平線を見つけてください
and then with the current location
そして現在の場所で
GPS corresponds to it
GPSが対応
There is one of these things
こういうことの一つがあるんです
pretty solid result
かなり堅実な結果
So it means
ということは、
as long as you will take him
あなたが彼を連れて行く限り
After you tell him some important notes
彼にいくつかの重要な注意事項を伝えた後、
have enough of
十分にある
data he can learn
彼が学ぶことができるデータ
After learning it, he can make this mark instead of you
それを学べば、彼はあなたの代わりにこのマークを付けることができます
In this way, your understanding of the article will be more and more marked
このようにして、記事の理解がさらに深まります
for you to understand
あなたが理解できるように
that paragraph of the article
記事のその段落
This story is easier to present
このストーリーはプレゼンテーションしやすいです
so
それで
just said
今言いました
There is his little story in one sentence
彼の小さな物語が一文の中にあります
sentence like a small sentence paragraph
小さな文の段落のような文
There is more in a paragraph
段落にはさらに続きがあります
But it's actually the way it starts and turns
しかし、実際にはそれが始まりと終わりの方法です。
can be learned
学ぶことができます
the same book
同じ本
Here's a gentleman after
これが紳士です
we probably don't have much time
おそらく時間があまりありません
Good idea, the question I want to ask is relatively basic
いい考えですね、私が聞きたい質問は比較的基本的なものです
implementation part
implementation的部分
Just now you mentioned that you need to mark
今、マークする必要があると言いました
that's there
それはそこにあります
The current mainstream trust understanding
現在主流の信頼理解
in you
あなたに
it may be used
使用されるかもしれません
Word to vet is to quantify these words
精査すべき言葉は、これらの言葉を数値化することです
Including these principles
これらの原則を含めて
Possibly also with phasors
おそらくフェーザーも使用可能
Then use some probability parameters
次に、いくつかの確率パラメータを使用します
is it here
ここですか
This imbedding or this
この埋め込みまたはこれ
Is there a label
ラベルはありますか
use this method
この方法を使用してください
this thing is very useful
これはとても便利です
but it is important to understand
しかし理解することが重要です
It actually does that kind of cluster
実際にそのようなクラスターを実行します
its comprehension comparison to those who understand
理解している人との理解度の比較
Not helpful, but he does a lot of tools that are very useful
役に立ちませんが、彼は非常に役立つツールをたくさん使っています
We now hope to have a new world full factor
私たちは今、新しいワールドフルファクターを期待しています
understandable
理解できる
It is also a vector, a vector that people can understand
それはベクトルでもある、人々が理解できるベクトルでもある
Then he has the same effect
そうすれば彼にも同じ効果がある
In this way, it can replace a vector that is now purely quantitative
このようにして、純粋に定量的なベクトルを置き換えることができます。
Then when he learns, his skills will be stronger
それで彼が学んだとき、彼のスキルはさらに強くなるでしょう
Then he marked it manually, Nano or machine learning
次に、Nano または機械学習で手動でマークを付けました
is the algorithm
アルゴリズムです
It's half manual and half learned.
それは半分マニュアルで半分学習です。
All have to be learned automatically, it is impossible to rely on people
すべて自動的に学習する必要があり、人に頼ることは不可能です
Excuse me
すみません
just heard you say that
あなたがそう言うのを聞いたばかりです
That is to say, let the so-called computer deal with the dead.
つまり、死者の処理をいわゆるコンピュータに任せるということです。
is getting easier
楽になってきています
The problem is that if you turn the living into the dead
問題は、生者を死者に変えてしまったら
According to your rigid method there should be a
あなたの厳格な方法によれば、
A very basic database
非常に基本的なデータベース
For example, the correspondence of words
たとえば、言葉の対応関係
There are so-called Chinese characters in the oriental characters
東洋文字にはいわゆる漢字もある
There are new Chinese characters
新しい漢字が登場しました
even privately printed Chinese characters
私的に印刷した漢字も
If you say these
これらを言うと
In the latest privately printed Chinese characters
最新の私字漢字では
So if it is in the information system of the China Theater Academy
中国演劇学院の情報システム内であれば
because of the word
その言葉のせいで
This so-called privately printed Chinese character is illiterate
このいわゆる私印刷の漢字は文盲です
Then all the expressions using privately printed Chinese characters
それから私用漢字を使ったすべての表現
the living
生きている
can never be
決してあり得ない
so-called information system
いわゆる情報システム
replace the dead aspect of the living
生きているものの死んだ側面を置き換える
Is it this way
こうですか
Now this is a
さて、これは
no shit problem
問題ないよ
That means we can do one thing today
つまり、今日できることは 1 つだけです
Because its influence is greater than one degree
その影響力は1度以上なので
Whether in academia or industry, we will be able to
学術界でも産業界でも、私たちは次のことができるようになります。
get enough money to do
するのに十分なお金を得る
so now say
だから今言ってください
any question
いかなる質問でも
Is it really that influential?
本当にそんなに影響力があるのでしょうか？
this is more important
これはもっと重要です
instead of saying this question
この質問を言う代わりに
does it make sense to some people
一部の人には意味が分かりますか
In fact, when we studied
実際、私たちが勉強していたとき、
In fact, we have many directions
実際、私たちには多くの方向性があります
So we ended up looking for a more capable
そこで私たちは、より高性能なものを探すことになりました。
There are funds and someone is willing to do it
資金はあるし、やりたい人はいる
like a lot of things you have money for
お金があるものはたくさんあるのと同じように
like can't find anyone to do
やってくれる人が見つからないような
Basically not easy to succeed
基本的に成功するのは簡単ではない
So this is a difficult place
だからここが難しいところなんです
i think i'll ask
聞いてみようと思います
last question
最後一個問題
Because of something you just said
あなたが今言ったことのせいで
There is something to learn first
まず学ぶべきことがある
because there is some learning
学びがあるから
merge it first
まずマージしてください
so where it starts
それでどこから始まるのか
is a very well defined
非常に明確に定義されています
a path
一個 path
because you already told him
あなたはすでに彼に言ったから
I'm going this way
私はここに行きます
we are many
私たちはたくさんいます
I think human speaking
人間が話していると思います
There is a great
素晴らしいものがあります
very special one
とても特別なもの
A key point is that people have the ability to create
重要な点は、人々には創造する能力があるということです。
That is to say, many of us are in the middle of the development of our science
つまり、私たちの多くは科学の発展の真っ只中にいます。
There are some paradigms
いくつかのパラダイムがあります
is that it is a jump
それはジャンプだということです
something new comes out
何か新しいものが出てくる
and then create a new field
そして新しいフィールドを作成します
so in this regard
したがって、この点に関して
It is the kind of creative we have now
それが今のクリエイティブです
Among the students, we often want to find
学生たちの間で、私たちはよく見つけたいと思っています。
something
何か
Now everyone is talking behind their backs
今、誰もが陰で話している
This thing can be learned
このことは学べる
or are you born
それとも生まれましたか
or what about your brain
あるいはあなたの脳はどうですか
so in this regard
したがって、この点に関して
Is it in the AI
AIの中にあるのか
Is there any research going on in this direction
この方向に進んでいる研究はありますか
This is now because its level is too high
これはレベルが高すぎるからです
That is to say, even if someone has researched
つまり、誰かが調べたとしても
I don't care about writing paper
原稿用紙には興味がない
because this is written
これが書いてあるから
debateable
議論の余地がある
That is, many people will argue
それは多くの人が議論するだろうということだ
disagree with it
それに同意しない
i think there must be
きっとあると思う
Like us I remember in the field of mathematics
私たちと同じように、私も数学の分野で覚えています
I see many examples
たくさんの例を見ます
What is set algebra in mathematics?
数学における集合代数とは何ですか?
He made some new discoveries , important prize - winning discoveries
彼はいくつかの新しい発見、重要な賞を受賞した発見をしました
It was he who brought some concept of geometry to that algebra
その代数学に幾何学の概念を持ち込んだのは彼でした
so he became famous
それで彼は有名になった
abstract substitution
抽象的な置換
We just had a gentleman ask
ある紳士から質問がありました
Say you see one sentence and think of another
ある文を見て別の文を思い浮かべたとします。
If that correspondence
その対応なら
Abstraction corresponds to the words you can rendezvous on the computer
抽象化はコンピュータ上でランデブーできる言葉に相当します
he can try
彼は試すことができる
Some of them might succeed when he tries.
彼が試みれば、そのうちのいくつかは成功するかもしれない。
So in fact they have someone running an experiment right now
実際、彼らは今実験を行っている人を抱えています
That is to say, he asked the computer to prove it.
つまり、彼はコンピュータにそれを証明するように頼んだのです。
But he simply let the computer generate such abstract things at will
しかし、彼は単にコンピューターにそのような抽象的なものを自由に生成させただけです
See if he can put him in the same way
彼も同じようにできるかどうか見てみる
It can be used in different places to prove some new theorems
いくつかの新しい定理を証明するためにさまざまな場所で使用できます
This theorem has never been proven
この定理は証明されたことがない
This kind of experiment is being done
このような実験が行われています
So maybe what you're talking about is a bit like
だから多分あなたが話していることは少し似ています
Then I would like to say that there is another question that is more related to daily life.
それから、もっと日常生活に関連した質問がもう一つあるということを申し上げたいと思います。
That is to say we are now online
つまり、私たちは今オンラインです
search or something
検索か何か
or inside your outer Broadder
または外側のBroadderの内側で
There is inside the browser
ブラウザの中にあります
i have a feeling say
言う気がする
i do everything now
私は今すべてをします
May be Google
可能都被Google
or what is collecting this information
またはこの情報を収集しているのは何ですか
So it means that he is learning to say
つまり、彼はこう言うことを学んでいるということです
i will do something
私は何かをします
collect this information
この情報を収集する
then analyze
それから分析します
Then I often find
そうするとよく見つけます
how to jump out of an ad
広告から飛び出す方法
It seems to be aimed at
を狙っているようです
This is a personalized ad
これはパーソナライズされた広告です
a reaction of
の反応
Now this thing is really going on
今、このことが本当に起こっている
or do we know
それとも私たちは知っていますか
what the hell is he doing
彼は一体何をしているのですか
none of us know
私たちの誰も知りません
We are practically all in every move
私たちはあらゆる動きにほぼ全員参加しています
There is a machine learning
機械学習というものがある
he wants to study later
彼は後で勉強したいと思っています
he wants to do something
彼は何かをしたいと思っています
This is actually in progress
これは実際に進行中です
this is so
これはとても〜です
that is
あれは
It is very strictly managed in Google
Google内で厳重に管理されております
That is to say, like our machine temple
つまり、私たちの機械の神殿のようなものです
Many of the letters we wrote are in it
私たちが書いた手紙がたくさん入っています
So it is absolutely not allowed to see
なので絶対に見ることは禁止です
but you can use a computer
でもコンピュータは使えます
program to read
読むプログラム
gentlemen
先生
To analyze, people can't see
分析するには、人は見ることができません
When is this information more dangerous?
この情報がより危険になるのはどのような場合ですか?
One day the U.S. government
ある日、アメリカ政府が
Trump went up and he said
トランプは立ち上がって言った
You give me all this personal information
あなたは私にこの個人情報をすべて教えてくれます
then you have to give
それならあなたは与えなければなりません
They are now the US government can go
彼らは今、米国政府が行くことができます
Ask his company for everything
すべてのことを彼の会社に尋ねる
Then how do you use this thing after you get it?
では、これを手に入れた後、どうやって使いますか？
then we don't know
それなら私たちには分かりません
So he will rely on this information in the future
したがって、彼は今後この情報に依存するでしょう
there are so many things to do
やるべきことがたくさんあります
As for the person in the ad
広告の中の人物に関しては
this is always done
これはいつも行われます
because it actually does no harm to the user
実際にユーザーに害を及ぼすものではないため、
So those of us Gmail stuff
つまり、Gmail に関するものは
Humans can't read but machines can
人間は読めないが機械は読める
So there are so many in the world
だから世界にはたくさんいるんだよ
When he read it, he didn't say
それを読んだとき、彼は何も言わなかった
For you personally, but read a general pattern
あなた個人向けですが、一般的なパターンをお読みください
to the general pattern
一般的なパターンに
he is not reading personal
彼は個人的なことを読んでいない
OK, let's do it today
よし、今日はそうしよう
It ends here
ここで終わります
thanks again
再度、感謝します
Xu said such a brilliant speech
徐さんはとても素晴らしいスピーチをしました